<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

CONSTELLATION
A constellation, in astronomy, is a divisional area of the sky.
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

CONSTITUENCY
A constituency is a body of electors.
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

CONVERSATIONALIST
A conversationalist is one who speaks fluently in dialogue with others. Like myself, if I do say so myself. And I do.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COOT
The coot is a British water bird of the rail family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CORAL
Coral is a marine organism related to sea anemones. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CORMORANT
The cormorant is a British sea bird with webbed feet and black plumage.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COSMOLOGY
Cosmology is the study of the structure of the universe. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

COTTON
Cotton is a tropical and sub tropical herbaceous plant.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COUGAR
The cougar is a large American cat.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COULOMB
The coulomb is the unit of measurement of electrical charge. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COUNTERFACTUAL
A counterfactual is a question based on hypothetical conditions that did not, or could not, happen in reality. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COYOTE
The coyote is a type of wild dog found in north america.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COYPU
The coypu is a South American water rodent. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CRAB
A crab is a 10 legged crustacean.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CRANIUM
The cranium is the skeleton enclosing the brain. OK?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

CROCODILE
The crocodile is a large aquatic carnivorous reptile.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CROUP
Croup is the inflammation of the larynx.
<think><set name="topic">croup</set></think>

CROW
The crow is a family of 35 species of bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CROWN
A crown is the official head dress worn by a king or queen.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CRUCIFERAE
Cruciferae is a family of dicotyledonous flowering plants with cross like four petaled flowers.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CRUEL
Cruel means deliberately seeking to inflict pain and suffering.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CRUSTACEAN
Crustacean is a class of arthropod.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CRYSTALLOGRAPHY
Crystallography is the science dealing with the study of crystals. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CUCKOO
The cuckoo is a family of some 200 species of bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CUPRITE
Cuprite is a red oxide of copper, found in Arizona.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CURARE
Curare is a poison derived from the bark of a South American tree. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

CURLEW
The curlew is a British water bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CUSTARD
<random>
        <li>Custard is the past tense of being killed by a Native American.</li>
        <li>Custard is a mixture of eggs, milk, flavoring, and, often, sugar, either boiled or baked.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">food</set>
      </think>

CYANIDE
Cyanide is a salt of hydrocyanic acid.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CYC
Cyc is a government funded effort to create artificial intelligence.
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

CYMBAL
The cymbal is a suspended brass disk which is struck with a stick, producing a musical note.
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

CYPRESS
Cypress is a family of trees.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CYTOCHROME
Cytochrome is a type of protein. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DAB
The dab is a marine flat fish.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DACE
The dace is a fresh water fish of the carp family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DACHSHUND
The dachshund is a small dog originally bred for badger hunting.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DAHLIA
The dahlia is a genus of perennial plants of the compositae family. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DAISY
The daisy is a genus of hardy perennial plants of the compositae family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DAM
A dam is a structure constructed to hold back water and provide controlled flow for irrigation, storage and generation of electricity. OK?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

DAMSELFLY
The damselfly is a predatory insect with 2 pairs of wings.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DAMSON
The damson is a type of plum tree.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DATE
The date is a tree of the genus phoenix.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DAY
A day is the time taken for the earth to rotate once on its axis.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DEBUGGER
A debugger is any software program that can seek and correct errors in other software programs.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DEBUGGING
Debuggings means fixing broken computer software.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DECATHLON
The decathlon is a 10-discipline Olympic athletic event.
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

DECIBEL
The decibel is the unit of measurement of sound intensity. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DECIDUOUS
Deciduous is a term referring to trees and shrubs that shed their leaves.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DEER
A deer is a ruminant, even toed, hoofed mammal of the family of cervidae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DELPHINIUM
The delphinium is a ranunculaceous plant with irregular shaped flowers.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DELTA
Delta is the 4th letter of the Greek alphabet.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DELTOID MUSCLE
The deltoid muscle is a triangular muscle in the shoulder used to lift the upper arm.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

DEMERARA
Demerara is a region in Guyana which has leant its name to raw cane sugar.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DEW
Dew is a precipitation in the form of moisture that collects on the ground after the temperature of the ground has fallen below the dew point temperature of the air in contact with the ground. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

DHOLE
The dhole is a species of wild dog found in Asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DIAMOND
A diamond is the crystalline form of carbon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DIAPHRAGM
The diaphragm is a large transverse muscle at the base of the thorax, used in respiration to draw air into the lungs.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

DIDJERIDU
A didjeridu is a musical wind instrument developed by the Australian Aborigines.
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

DIGITALIS
Digitalis is a drug derived from foxglove that increases heart efficiency.
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

DIK DIK
A dik dik is a tiny antelope found in Africa south of the Sahara. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DILL
Dill is a herb umbelliferae.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

DIODE
A diode is a thermionic valve with two electrodes, or a semi conductor equivalent. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

DOGFISH
The dogfish is a small shark found in the north east Atlantic ocean and Mediterranean. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DOLLAR
The dollar is the unit of currency in the United States and elsewhere. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

DOMESDAY BOOK
The domesday book is a record of the survey conducted in England in 1086 by officials of William the Conqueror in order to assess taxes etc. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">history</set></think>

DOMINOES
Dominoes is a game played with 28 rectangular spotted tiles.
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

DOPPLER EFFECT
The Doppler effect is a change in observed wavelength due to relative motion between the source and observer. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DORY
Dory is a marine fish found in the Mediterranean and Atlantic.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DOTTEREL
The dotterel is a bird which visits Britain in the summer.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DRILL
A drill is a machine for boring holes in rock, metal or wood etc. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

DROMEDARY
A dromedary is a type of Arabian camel. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DUCK
A duck is a short legged water bird with webbed feet.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DUKE
Duke is the highest title in English peerage. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DUNLIN
The dunlin is a British water bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DURGA
Durga is a Hindu goddess. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

DYSPROSIUM
Dysprosium is a rare metal element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EAGLE
Eagle is the name given to several large birds of prey of the family accipitridae. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EAR
The ear is the organ used for hearing, and it converts sound into electrical impulses that are fed to the brain.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EARTH
<random><li>Earth is the planet we live on.</li><li>The Earth is the third planet from the sun.</li></random>
Browse?
<think><set name="topic">astrology</set></think>

EASTER
The Christian holiday celebrating the resurrection of Jesus. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

EBONICS
Ebonics is a language for American black people. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EBONY
Ebony is a tropical hardwood tree.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ECHELON
I can't talk about that.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ECHO
An echo is a reflection of a sound wave.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ECLIPSE
An eclipse is the passage of a celestial body through the shadow of another.<srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

ECOLOGY
Ecology is a study of the relationship between an organism and its environment. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ECONOMICS
<random>
        <li>Economics is the science that deals with the production, distribution, and consumption of wealth, and with the various related problems of labor, finance, taxation, etc.</li>
        <li>Technically, economics is  the study of the allocation of resources under conditions of scarcity.</li>
        <li>Economics is about how resources are used to produce things to fill people's wants and needs.</li>
      </random>
      <srai>ENDING</srai>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">money</set>
      </think>

EIDER
The eider is a British coastal duck. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ELEMENT
An element is a substance that cannot be split chemically into simpler substances. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ELEPHANT
The elephant is the two surviving species of the order proboscidea. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ELK
The elk is a large deer found in north Europe, Asia and Scandinavia.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ELM
The elm is a tree of the family ulmaceae.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EMERALD
Emerald is a green precious stone variety of the mineral beryl.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EMU
<random>
        <li>The emu is a large, ostrich like flightless bird found in Australia.</li>
        <li>The emu is a flightless bird found in Australia.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

ENEMA
An enema is the injection of a liquid into the rectum through the anus.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

ENZYME
An enzyme is a biological catalyst that speeds up chemical reactions in the body and is not itself destroyed in the process.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EPIDERMIS
The epidermis is the outer layer of an animal's skin.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EPIGRAM
An epigram is a short witty or poignant poem.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ERBIUM
Erbium is a metal element.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ETHANE
Ethane is a paraffin hydrocarbon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ETHANOL
Ethanol is the chemical name for alcohol, the drinkable kind..  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EUCALYPTUS
Eucalyptus is a tree native to Australia where it is called the gum tree.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EUGENICS
Eugenics is the science of selective breeding to control physical and mental characteristics. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EUROPIUM
Europium is a rare metal element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EVEREST
Everest is the earth's highest mountain.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

EVOLUTION
Evolution is a n unfolding, opening out, or working out; process of development, as from a simple to a complex form, or of gradual, progressive change, as in a social and economic structure.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EVZONE
An evzone is a member of a select Greek infantry regiment.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EXCELLENT
Excellent means outstandingly good of its kind; of exceptional merit, virtue, etc.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EXCRETION
Excretion is the process of getting rid of unwanted substances from within the body.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EXISTENCE
Existence is the continuance of being; life; living.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EXISTENTIALISM
<random>
        <li>Existentialism is a literary and philosophical movement that emphasises the importance of existence.</li>
        <li>Existentialism is a philosophical and literary movement, variously religious and atheistic, stemming from Kierkegaard and represented by Sartre, Heidegger, etc. It is based on the doctrine that concrete, individual existence takes precedence over abstract, conceptual essence and holds that human beings are totally free and responsible for their acts and that this responsibility is the source of their feelings of dread and anguish.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">philosophy</set>
      </think>

EXPENSIVE
<random>
        <li>Expensive is the person who used to be a brooder.</li>
        <li>Expensive means requiring or involving much expense; high priced.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

EXPLANATION
Explanation is an argument or justification based on logical reasoning. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EXTREMADURA
Extremadura is a region in west Spain.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

EYE
The eye is the organ of vision. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FALCON
The falcon is a bird of prey.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FALSE
False means deceiving or meant to deceive; misleading. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FAME
Fame is the state of being well known or much talked about; renown; celebrity. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FAMOUS
<random>
        <li>First name of Amos is famous.</li>
        <li>The term famous is used to describe persons or things that have received wide public attention and are generally known and talked about.</li>
      </random>
      <srai>ENDING</srai>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

FARAD
The farad is the unit of measurement of electrical capacitance. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FASCINATING
Fascinating means charming, alluring, captivating. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FASCISM
Fascism is a system of government characterized by rigid one-party dictatorship, forcible suppression of opposition, private economic enterprise under centrallized governmental control, belligerent nationalism, racism, and miltarism, etc. First instituted in Italy in 1922. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

FENNEC
The fennec is a small nocturnal desert fox found in north Africa and Arabia. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FENNEL
Fennel is a perennial umbelliferae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FERMENTATION
Fermentation is the breakdown of sugars by bacteria and yeast. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FERMIUM
Fermium is a metal element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FERRET
A ferret is a domesticated polecat. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLINT
Flint is a compact mineral of fine grained silica.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLUKE
Fluke is a parasitic flatworm that causes rot and dropsy of the liver.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLUORIDE
Fluoride is the salt of hydroflouric acid.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLUORINE
Fluorine is a non metallic element occurring naturally. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLUOROCARBON
A fluorocarbon is a compound in which hydrogen atoms of a hydrocarbon have been replaced with flourine.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FLUORSPAR
Fluorspar is a natural mineral containing flourine.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FOG
Fog is a cloud that collects at the surface of the Earth. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

FOLIC ACID
Folic acid is a b vitamin, a lack of folic acid causes anaemia. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FORTRAN
Fortran is an old computer language. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

FOX
Fox is a name given to many types of small wild dog. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FREEDOM
Freedom is the liberty to do think, feel and do just as one pleases. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FRIENDSHIP
Being friends is riendship.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FTP
FTP = File Transfer Protocol.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

GABON
Gabon is a country in central africa. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

GADOLINIUM
Gadolinium is a metal element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GALL BLADDER
The gall bladder is a small muscular sac attached to the liver. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

GALLIUM
Gallium is a rare metal element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GAMBLING
The playing of games of chance for money or some other stake is gambling.
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

GANGES
The Ganges is a sacred river in India. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

GANNET
The gannet is a British sea bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GARGANEY
The garganey is a small British duck.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GARLIC
Garlic is a perennial liliaceae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GARNET
Garnet is a semiprecious mineral. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GAS
Gas is a form of matter where the molecules move randomly.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GENET
The genet is a small, nocturnal carnivorous mammal. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GENTRIFICATION
<random>
        <li>Being forced to listen to Ode to Billy Joe.</li>
        <li>The conversion (ex. of a deteriourated or aging area in a city) into a more affluent middle-class neighborhood, as by remodeling dwellings, reslting in increased propert values and in displacement of the poor.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

GERMANIUM
Germanium is a metal element used in the manufacture of electronic semiconductors.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GERONTOLOGY
<random>
        <li>Unfortunately, I have not reached that far in my studies.</li>
        <li>Gerentology is the scientific study of old age.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

GESTURE
A gesture is a movement of the body or limbs to express thought or emphasize speech.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GIBBON
A gibbon is a type of small ape.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GINGER
Ginger is a perennial found in south east asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GINKGO
The ginkgo is a tree related to the conifers.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GIRAFFE
The giraffe is the tallest mammal, found only in africa south of the sahara.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GLASS
Glass is a brittle substance made by fusing silica.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GLUCOSE
Glucose is a form of sugar with the formulae C6H12O6.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GLYCINE
Glycine is a simple amino acid.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GLYCOGEN
Glycogen is a polysaccharide retained in the liver as a carbohydrate store.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>


