<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ORB
ORB = object request broker, the primary message routing component in a CORBA product RMI Remote Method Invocation, the Java standard technology for building distributed objects whose methods can be invoked remotely across a network
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OVARIES
The ovaries are two organs that store eggs in a woman's body and produce hormones associated with sex and reproduction.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

PARAMETERS
A parameter is a constant in an equation, formula or program that varies in more general forms of the same computation.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PELVIS
The pelvis is a bony girdle in vertebrates that connects the body with the lower extremities.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

POLKA
The polka is a lively Bohemian folk dance.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PRIORI
<random>
        <li>A priori is Latin for "before the fact", meaning something that is obviously or self-evidently true.</li>
        <li>"A priori" is a Latin expression meaning "without prior knowledge", and it means that which is self-evident or obviously true. Like, a triangle has three sides, a priori.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

PROFITABLE
Profitable means making money in the stock market.
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

PROTOPLASM
Protoplasm is the basic living substance of all animals.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PST
PST = Pacific Standard Time
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RECTUM
<random>
        <li>The rectum is the lowest portion of the large intestine, terminating at the anus.</li>
        <li>The rectum is tthe lowest end of the bowel before the anus, where feces is stored.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

RED DWARF
A red dwarf is a cool, faint star.
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

RHETORICAL
A rhetorical question is one you don't really expect an answer to.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RHYTHM
Rhythm is the beat behind a piece of music.
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

SERVLET
A servlet is an application extension to a Java Web server
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

SKELETON
The skeleton is the hard internal or external framework of bones.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

SOCCER
Soccer is a game played with a round ball by two teams of eleven players on a field with a goal at either end; the ball is moved chiefly by kicking or by using any part of the body except the hands and arms.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SOUNDCARD
The audio system on your computer is a soundcard
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

SPECULUM
A speculum is a plastic or metal instrument used to push back the walls of the vagina so the clinician can examine the vagina and cervix.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

TABLES
Tables are a compact, systematic list of details, contents, etc. A compact arrangement of related facts,  figures, values, etc. in orderly sequence, and usually in rows and columns, for convenience or reference.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

THE ALPHABET
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ is the alphabet.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

THE ANSWER
The answer is the correct reply to the question.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

THEY
They means persons, animals, or things previously mentioned.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TORPEDO
A torpedo is a missile which swims through water to its target.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

UMBRELLA
An umbrella is a light, portable screen usually circular and supported on a central stick.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

URETHRA
The urethra is the tube from the bladder to the opening from which men and women urinate.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

URINE
Urine is a fluid produced by the kidneys.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

UTERUS
The uterus is the pear-shaped reproductive organ from which women menstruate and where normal pregnancy develops.
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

VENUS
In Roman Mythology, the goddess of love and beauty; identified with the Greek Aphrodite.  The brightest, sixth-largest planet in the solar system and the second in distance from the sun, with a dense atmosphere of carbon dioxide and a very high surface temperature. Its diameter is circa 12,100 km (circa 7,520 miles). Its period of revolution is circa 225 earth days. Its period of rotation (retrograde), is 243.01 earth days.   Also used to label a very beautiful woman.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

VULVA
The vulva is a woman's external sex organs, including the clitoris, the labia, and opening to the vagina.
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

WAIST
The waist is the part of the body between the ribs and the hips.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WEBTV
<random>
        <li>A WebTV is a way of accessing the world wide web without making an investment in a full PC.</li>
        <li>WebTV is TV-based internet service from Microsoft.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

WEED
A weed is any undersired, uncultivated plant, especially growing in profusion so as to crowd out a desired crop, disfigure a lawn, etc.  Also a term for marijuana.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>


