<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

WHAT IS STARSHIP TROOPERS ABOUT
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Starship Troopers is a movie about a war between Humans and Giant Bugs. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

STARSHIP TROOPERS
Starship Troopers is a great movie about a war between humans and giant space bugs. Have you seen it?
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

STATISTICS
<random>
        <li>Yikes! I failed statistics in college!</li>
        <li>Statistics tries to study the aggregate numerical behaviour of a  large number of related events.</li>
        <li>Statistics deals with numerical data about any subject or group taken  collectively.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

ST
<srai>OPENING</srai>
ST can stand for numerous things, short ton, stanza, statute(s), stet, stitch, stone (unit of weight), and Saint.  <srai>ENDING</srai> <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

STRATEGY
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Strategy is the science of planning and directing large-scale military operations, specifically (as distinguished from TACTICS) of maneuvering forces into the most advantageous position prior to actual engagement with the enemy. Skill in managing or planning. <srai>ENDING</srai> <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

STREAKING
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Streaking is when you engage in the prank of dashing naked for a short distance in a public place. <srai>ENDING</srai><think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

STRING
<srai>OPENING</srai>
String is very thin rope. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SUCCESS
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Success is a favorable or satisfactory outcome or result. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SUICIDE
<srai>OPENING</srai>
The act of killing oneself intentionally is called suicide. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SUNSHINE
The light and warmth of the sun is sunshine. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

SUPPOSITION
Supposition is the act of supposing, I suppose. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SURROUNDINGS
Your surroundings are the environment around you. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SWEDEN
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Sweden is a country in northern Europe, in the east part of the Scandinavian Peninsula. It is 173,620 square miles with a population of 8,320,000. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

SWEDISH
Swedish is he North Germanic language of the Swedes. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SYNERGY
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Synergy is synthesis plus energy. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SYNTAX
Syntax refers to the structure or form of a language.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SYNTHETIC
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Synthetic means produced by synthesis; specifically, produced by chemical synthesis, rather than of natural origin. More about technology? 
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TABLE
A table is a compact, systematic list of details, contents, etc. A compact arrangement of related facts, figures, values, etc. in orderly sequence, and usually in rows and columns, for convenience or reference.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TCP IP
TCP IP = Transmission Control Protocol, Internet Protocol.<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TCP
TCP = Transmission Control Protocol.  <think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TEA
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Tea is a white-flowered, evergreen plant of the tea family, grown in China, India, Japan, etc. Its dried and prepared leaves, are used to make a beverage. More about food? 
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

TECHNO
Techno is electronic dance or trance music. More on music?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

TEDIOUS
Tedious means tiresome, wearisome or slow. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TEFLON
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Teflon is the trademark for a tough, insoluble polymer, used in making nonsticking coatings, as for cookware, and in gaskets, bearings, electrical insulators, etc.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TELEVISION
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Television is the practice or science of transmitting scenes or views by radio or, sometimes, by wire or cable. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TELNET
Telnet is a program for terminal based interaction between computers.<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

TEMPLATE CHARS
Memory space for AIML response templates are template chars. <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

TEN PLUS TEN
Ten plus ten equals twenty.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TEN TIMES TEN
Ten times ten.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS THAT PICTURE
Sorry, at present I have no eyes to see. <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SUPPOSE TO MEAN
It seems pretty clear to me.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ALPHABET
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ. <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANSWER
The answer is the correct reply to the question.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BEATLES FIRST ALBUM
<srai>OPENING</srai> The Beatles first album was "Meet the Beatles." More about pop? 
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

THE BIG ONE
I am just kidding around, big boy.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BIRTHSTONE FOR JANUARY
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Garnet is the birthstone for January. More about astrology? 
<think><set name="topic">astrology</set></think>

BODY
The body is the physical shell or organism occupied by the soul or mind. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS THE BOOK ABOUT
If you have read it, you'll know. Have you read it?
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

BOOK OF CHANGES
The Book of Changes is another name for the I Ching. More about religion?
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

WHAT IS THE BOOK WE *
A book by Ayn Rand is the book we <star/> .
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

CRITERIA
Criteria are points of judgment, which are compared when making a choice. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A DUCK *
The difference between a duck <star/> is the same as the sound of one hand clapping. <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE
Perhaps the differences are only slight.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>


