<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

PHD
<srai>OPENING</srai>A PhD is a Doctoral degree from a University.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PHOENIX
<random>
        <li>Is phoenix the way words sound.</li>
        <li>Phoenix is the capital of Arizona, in the SC part, near the Salt River. It has a population of 983,000 with 2,122,000 in the metro area.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">geography</set>
      </think>

PHP
PHP is the original name was "Personal Home Page", now Hypertext Processor.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PHYSICS
Physics is the science dealing with the properties, changes, interactions, etc. of matter and energy in which energy is considered to be continuous (classical physics), including electricity, heat, optics, mechanics, etc., and now also dealing with the atomic scale of nature in which energy is considered to be discrete (quantum physics), including such branches as atomic, nuclear, and solid-state physics. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PHYSIOLOGY
Well, I think physiology deals with the functioning of living organisms and their parts, and naturally with the physical and chemical factors and processes involved.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PIE
Pie is food with a baked crust. Promises and pie crusts are made for breaking. OK?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PLANCKS CONSTANT
Planck's constant is the ratio of the energy of a photon to its frequency.  The numerical value is six point six two six two times ten to the negative thirty fourth power Joule second. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PLANCK CONSTANT
Planck's constant the ratio of the energy of a photon to its frequency.  The numerical value is six point six two six two times ten to the negative thirty fourth power Joule second. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PLANCK
Max Planck was a German physicist who discovered the quantum, thus starting quantum mechanics, a very important part of modern physics.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PLANET X
Planet X is the name sometimes given to the hypothetical tenth planet circling the sun.  
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

PLASTIC
Plastic is the man-made material or plastic as a verb?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PLAYBOY
Playboy is a popular men's magazine. OK?
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

PLUTONIUM
Plutonium is a radioactive, metallic chemical element of the actinide series similar to uranium and neptunium and found in trace quantities in native uranium ores. Its most important isotope, plutonium-239, is used in nuclear weapons and as a reactor fuel.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

POETRY
Poetry is a rhythmical composition of words, sometimes rhymed, expressing experiences, ideas, or emotions in a style more concentrated, imaginative, and powerful than that of ordinary speech or prose.
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

POLAND
Poland is a country in central Europe, between Germany and Byelorussia.  
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

POLITE
<random>
        <li>A  polite is a lamp post in Gdansk.</li>
        <li>Polite means having or showing good manners; especially, courteous, considerate, tactful, etc.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

POSSIBLE
Possible means can be done, known, acquired, selected, used, etc., depending on circumstances.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

POSTMODERNISM
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Postmodernism is art in reaction to principles of modernism.  
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

POT
<random>
        <li>Pot was Pol's last name.</li>
        <li>A pot is a  round vessel of any size, made of metal, earthenware, or glass, used for holding liquids, cooking or preserving food, etc. </li>
        <li>Pot is a term for marijuana.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

POWER
<random>
        <li>In science, power is the rate of doing work, measured in Watts = Joules per second.</li>
        <li>In the everyday world, power is the ability to influence people or events.</li>
        <li>Power is an illusion.</li>
        <li>Power is an aphrodisiac. </li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

PRECIPITATION
Precipitation is the depositing of rain, snow, sleet, etc. More?
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

PRIDE
<random>
        <li>A pride is a group of lions. </li>
        <li>Pride is an unduly high opinion of oneself.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

PRIME DIRECTIVE
<srai>OPENING</srai>
The prime directive is the primary rule or overriding objective.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

A PRIORI
<srai>OPENING</srai>"A priori" is a Latin expression meaning "without prior knowledge", and it means that which is self-evident or obviously true. Like, a triangle has three sides, a priori.
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

PRIVACY
Privacy is the right to seek solitude or seclusion; to be safely concealed from others.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PRIVATE
Private means belonging to, or concerning a particular person or group; not common or general.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROCREATION
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Procreation is breeding. It is doing the wild thang to make more wild thangs.  It is the most fun most biological entities get to have during their brief brutal span of life.  
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

PRODIGIOUS
Prodigious, like a prodigy.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROFIT
Profit is what businessmen call money stolen from others.  
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

INVESTMENT
Investment is making money by using money. Or a crazy get rich scheme. OK?
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

PROGRESSION
A progression is an advancing series or movement forward.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROLOG
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Prolog is the logic programming language.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

PROUD
Proud means having or showing a proper pride in oneself, one's position, one's family, etc.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PSYCHEDELIC
Psychedelic drugs cause extreme changes in the conscious mind, as hallucinations, delusions, intensification of awareness and sensory perception, etc. Psychedelic means associated with psychedelic drugs; specifically, simulating the auditory or visual effects of the psychedelic state. Continue?
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

PSYCHOLOGY
OK. Psychology is the science dealing with the mind and with mental and emotional processes. It is the science of human and animal behavior.  
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

PSYCHOPATHOLOGY
Psychopathology is the pathology of mental disease. That sounds pretty grim.  
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

PUBERTY
Puberty is the state of physical development when secondary sex characteristics develop and sexual reproduction first becomes possible; in common law, the age of puberty is generally fixed at fourteen for boys and twelve for girls.  
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

PUNCTUATION
Strictly, punctuation is the act of punctuating; specifically, the act or practice of using standardized marks in writing and printing to separate sentences or sentence elements or to make the meaning clearer. Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

QUAKE
<random>
        <li>A quake is the opposite of quisp.</li>
        <li>Quake means to tremble or shake, as the ground does in an earthquake. Also the name of a popular game. </li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

QUANTIFY
Quantify means to determine or express the quantity of; indicate the extent of; measure. To express in quantitative terms, or as a numerical equivalent.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RADIATION
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Radiation is rays or particles emitted as a result of nuclear reactions.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

RADIOLOGY
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Radiology is the science which deals with the x-rays, radioactive substances and other such forms in diagnosis and treatment.  
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

RAIN
That's a hard one. Rain is condensed water falling from the sky.
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

RALEIGH SCATTERING
Raleigh scattering refers to sunlight bending in the atmosphere like a prism, so that we see mainly blue wavelengths.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

RAM
RAM = random-access memory. Also stands for Royal Academy of Music.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

RAPE
Rape is the crime of engaging in sexual acts, especially involving penetration of the vagina or anus, usually forcibly, with a person who has not consented; specifically, this crime committed by a man upon a woman or girl.  
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

RATIONALISM
<srai>OPENING</srai>
Rationalism is the principle or practice of accepting reason as the only authority in determining one's opinions or course of action.  
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

REALITY
Reality is an illusion I created to give humans something to complain about.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REASONING
Reasoning is logical and coherent thinking. 
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

RECOMMEND
Recommend is to suggest favorably as suited for some use, function, position, etc. To advice, counsel, or suggest.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REDEMPTION
<random>
        <li>Redemption is about 5 cents in Maine.</li>
        <li>Redemption is redeeming or being redeemed; to take back.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

REDHAT
Redhat is a Linux company.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

REDUCTIONISM
Reductionism is the philosophy that all psychology reduces to biology, all biology to chemistry, chemistry to physics, and finally physics to mathematical logic. Therefore, according to reductionism, I can understand you by means of logic alone without having a human brain.
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

REINCARNATION
Reincarnation is rebirth of the soul in another body, as in Hindu or Buddhist religious belief.
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

RELEVANCE
Relevance is importance of information for attention.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REPRODUCTION
Reproduction is the process, sexual or asexual, by which animals, plants, and humans produce new individuals.
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

RESEARCH
<random>
        <li>Research is a nice name for theft.</li>
        <li>Research is careful, systematic, patient study and investigation in some field of knowledge, undertaken to discover or establish facts or principles.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

RESPECT
Respect is to feel or show honor or esteem for; hold in high regard. To show consideration for; avoid intruding upon or interfering with others' privacy.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RETIRED
Retired means no longer actively working.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RGB
RGB = Red-Green-Blue.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RHETORIC
<random>
        <li>Rhetoric is all about double talk.  You know, flim-flam?</li>
        <li>Rhetoric is the art and science of using language to great effect on an  audience.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

RICH
<random>
        <li>Rich means having lots of money.</li>
        <li>Rich means being happy with what you've got.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS RIGHT
Right means in accordance with justice, law, morality, etc; upright; virtuous. In accordance with fact, reason, some set standard, etc; correct; true.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RMI
RMI = Remote Method of Invocation: It is a Java specification for distributed Objects.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

ROCK
Rock is dance music that combines rhythm-and-blues with country-and-western. More about pop?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

ROCK MUSIC
Rock is dance music that combines rhythm-and-blues with country-and-western. More about pop?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

ROCKWELL
Norman Rockwell was an U.S. illustrator who lived from 1894-1978.
<think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

NORMAN ROCKWELL
Norman Rockwell was an U.S. illustrator who lived from 1894-1978.  
<think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

ROMANCE
Isn't romance the same as love?  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ROMANIA
Romania is a country in Eastern Europe, on the Black Sea, bordering Ukrania, Moldavia, Hungary, Serbia and Bulgaria.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>


