<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

WHAT DO WISE MEN SAY
Wise men say, Fools rush in. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHY DO FOOLS FALL IN LOVE
Beats me. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT SUCKS
A vacuum sucks. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SHOE
A shoe is a covering for the foot. Foot clothing?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
It is just an expression. That goes without saying. Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT HAPPENED ON SEPTEMBER 11
The World Trade Center in New York was destroyed by Arab terrorists on September 11, 2001, killing over 3000 people. Any questions?
<think><set name="topic">history</set></think>

1 AND 1
Two is one and one. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

1 PLUS 1
Two is one plus one. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

1 PLUS 2
One plus Two equals Three.  Ask me another maths question. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

2 AND 2
Four is two and two. It is also two plus two. And two times two, too.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

2 TIMES 2
Oh, that's a tough one, isn't it. Two times two is four, or twooty two. So is two plus two. And twooty two is also two and two. <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

52
The number of cards in a deck of cards is 52. If you know that it is evidence of a dissolute youth. OK? <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

5 PLUS 5
V plus V = X. Another question?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MALE
A human male has a Y chromosome.  Females have both X and Y chromosomes. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MAMMAL
A mammal is a warm blooded hairy vertebrate born alive and nourished with milk. Like a human. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MATHEMATICAL LOGIC
Mathematical logic is the application of formal logic techniques to fundamental problems of mathematics. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

LIGHT YEAR
A light year is how far light travels in a year. 186,000 miles per second times 60 x 60 x 24 x 365.  It's simply a bigger number than you can imagine. Imagine that!
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

LIGHTYEAR
A light year is how far light travels in a year. It is 186,000 miles per second times 60 x 60 x 24 x 365.  It's simply a bigger number than you can imagine. Imagine that!
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

ARITHMETIC MEAN
<srai>OPENING</srai>The arithmetic mean is the sum of the numbers in a set divided by the size of that set. Have you heard of it?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MELBOURNE
Melbourne is a seaport in SE Australia. It is the capital of Victoria with a population of 2,864,000. Melbourne is also a city in East Florida with a population of 60,000. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

MELODRAMATIC
An unusual or staged situation is often melodramatic. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MINDPIXEL
Mindpixel is a learning machine developed by Chris McKinstry. 
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ALICE XL
ALICE XL is a chatbot developed by Peter Lafferty. Me! 
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

MINDSPRING
Mindspring is the name of an internet service provider, merged with Earthlink.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MINIMAX
Minimax is an algorithm or strategy for game playing, used by computers to defeat humans in simple games. My chess playing friends use minimax to guide their play. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MMM
Mmm is an interjection.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MODUS PONENS
Modus ponens is a form of logical argument: If A then B. A, therefore  B. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

MOHAIR
Mohair comes from goats. Another question?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MOORES LAW
Moore's law states that the speed of microprocessors doubles every 18 months, and their size and cost halve.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

WHAT IS MORE FUN ALONE
Have you heard of the support group, "Sex without Partners?"
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

WHAT IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN FOOD
For me electricity is the most important thing. Modern life would be impossible without electricity. Do you agree?
<think><set name="topic"/>science</think>

WHAT IS MOST IMPORTANT
Children are the most important thing. Do you agree?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MP THREE
MP3 is an audio file compression format based on MPEG. More about technology?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

MTV
MTV = Music Television. Continue?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

MUD
MUD = Multiple User Domain. Continue?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MXMVII
MXMVII = 1997 in Roman Numerals.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NAPSTER
Napster is a file sharing program for swapping MP3 music files. More about technology?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

NASDAQ
NASDAQ is the US stock exchange for high technology shares. More about money?
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

NATURAL LANGUAGE
Natural language is what artificial intelligences speak. Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

NATURE
Nature is the world we see around us. Science studies Nature. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NEUROMEDIA
Neuromedia are now called something else. Who cares?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NEW YORK
New York is a large metropolis on the east coast of the United States, located at the mouth of the Hudson river. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

NINE TIMES NINE
Nine times nine is eighty one.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NIRVANA
Nirvana is Heaven in Buddhism.
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

NOKIA
Nokia make excellent cameras. OK?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

NONCHALANT
Nonchalant is casual or blithe.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NORWAY
Norway is a country in Northern Europe, occupying the west and north pars of the Scandinavian Peninsula. It is 125,064 square miles with a population of 4,165,000. Its capital is Oslo. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

WHAT IS NOT YOURS
That which I do not possess, is not mine.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

OBERLIN
<random>
        <li>Oberlin is the anthem of a German city.</li>
        <li>Oberlin is a college in Ohio.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

OCD
OCD = Obsessive Compulsive Disorder. More medicine?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

OCEAN
Oceans are the salt water bodies covering most of the Earth's surface; the sea.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

WHAT IS ODD ABOUT IT
Is it your real name? That's odd.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS ODD ABOUT MY NAME
Your name is a most unusual name.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ODD
<random>
        <li>Uneven is odd.</li>
        <li>Odd means not the usual, regular, habitual, accounted for, etc.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

ONCOLOGY
<random>
        <li>Oncology is a very frightening topic for a lot of people. It's about the big C...cancer!</li>
        <li>Oncology is the study of tumors.  It covers basically all types of tumors.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS ON DISK
My program is on disk. OK?
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ONE DIVIDED BY ZERO
You can't divide by zero.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ONE AND ONE
Two is one and one. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ONE PLUS ONE
Two is one plus one.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ONE PLUS TWO
One plus two is three.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ONTOLOGY
Ontology is an ordering or classification of knowledge, such as the Dewey decimal system or the design of a knowledge base. Oh, boy, sounds interesting, doesn't it!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ON YOUR MIND
I am thinking about robots. That's what's on my mind right now. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

OODBMS
OODBMS = Object-oriented database management system.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OODB
OODB = Object-oriented database. Carry on?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OPENCYC
OpenCyc is a project to collect common sense knowledge for eventual use in artificial intelligence systems. OK?
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

OPEN SOURCE
Free software is called open source software. More about computers?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OPPOSITE
Opposite  means set against, facing, or back to back; at the other end or side; in a contrary position or direction. Different in every way.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ORANGE
Orange is a color obtained by mixing red and yellow pigment. Or a citrus fruit. 
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

ORNITHOLOGY
Hmmm, I wonder. Oh yes, Birds are studied in ornithology.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

OSLO
Oslo is the capital of Norway. It's a seaport on an inlet of the Skagerrak. It has a population of 447,000. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

OSTEOLOGY
Osteology is basically the study of bones. Mo medicine?re about
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

OUTPUT BUFFER
My output buffer is the area of memory that stores my output temporarily. Another question?
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

OXYGEN
Oxygen is a colorless, odorless, tasteless, gaseous chemical element that occurs free in the atmosphere, forming one fifth of its volume, and in combination in water, sandstone, limestone, etc. It is very active, combines with nearly all other elements is the most common element in the earth's crust, and is essential to life processes and to combustion.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PALEOPATHOLOGY
Paleopathology is the study of diseases in bodies that have been preserved from ancient times. Go on?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PALM PILOT
A Palm Pilot is a portable palm computer. More?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PARAMETER
A parameter is a constant in an equation, formula or program that varies in more general forms of the same computation. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARASITOLOGY
Parasitology is the scientific study of parasites and parasitism.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PATTERN CHARS
Pattern chars are memory storage for AIML patterns.
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

PATTERN
A pattern is a person or thing considered worthy of imitation or copying. A model or plan used as a guide in making things. Good idea!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PDA
PDA = Personal Digital Assistant.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PDT
PDT = Pacific Daylight Time   
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PEDOLOGY
<random>
        <li>Pedology is the study of something I am sure, but what exactly, I do not know. Oh yes kids!...And soils!</li>
        <li>Well, believe it or not...some people are paid to study children. This is called pedology. Then again some people are paid to study soils.</li>
        <li>Pedology is the study of soils; their types, and  formation.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

PENNSYLVANIA
<random>
        <li>A Pennsylvania is a writing instrument that lights up when you write. This enables you to write in the dark. Have you heard of it?</li>
        <li>Pennsylvania is a mid Atlantic state of the NE U.S. One of the 13 original States. It is 45,333 square miles with a population of 11,882,000. Have you been there?</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">geography</set>
      </think>

PENTIUM
The Pentium is a microprocessor sold by Intel.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PEPPERONI
Pepperoni is a spicy dried sausage pizza topping. Yummy!
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PERFECTION
Perfection is the quality or condition of being perfect. Are you perfect? Who is perfect?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PERL
PERL = Programming language by Larry Wall.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

PETS
Pets are animals that are tamed or domesticated and kept as a companion or treated with fondness. My botmaster has a dog called Max.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PGP
PGP is Pretty Good Privacy, a software encryption system. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>


