<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

MORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

BROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

GO TO TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

CAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

SHALL WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

LETS TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

LET S TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

TALK TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

TELL ME TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

NO MORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NO TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

* NO TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NO TECHNOLOGY *
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

_ NO * TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NO * TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NO _ TECHNOLOGY *
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NOT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

* NOT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NOT TECHNOLOGY *
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

_ NOT * TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

I AM NOT INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

IM NOT INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

I M NOT INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NOT INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

_ NOT INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

YESMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

* YESMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YES *MORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

_ YES *MORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YUPMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YAHMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YEAHMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

OKMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

NOMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

* NOMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NO *MORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NUPMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NAHMORE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

YESMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

* YESMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YES *MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

_ YES *MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YUPMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YAHMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YEAHMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

OKMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY</srai>

NOMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

* NOMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NO *MORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NUPMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NAHMORE ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

YESIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

* YESIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YES *IS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

_ YES *IS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YUPIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YAHIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YEAHIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

* NOIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NO *IS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

_ NO *IS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NUPIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

NAHIS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
<srai>CHANGE TOPIC</srai>

*IS THIS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YESARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

* YESARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YES *ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

_ YES *ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YUPARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YAHARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

YEAHARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
Can we talk about technology?

* NOARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NO *ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

_ NO *ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NUPARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NAHARE YOU INTERESTED IN TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

YESCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

* YESCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YES *CAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

_ YES *CAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YUPCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YAHCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YEAHCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

OKCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

OH YESCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

WHY NOTCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

OF COURSECAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

GO AHEADCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

CARRY ONCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

PLEASE DOCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

YES PLEASECAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

GO ONCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

GO ON THENCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

ALRIGHTCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

SURECAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

ALLRIGHTCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY</srai>

NOCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

* NOCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NUPCAN WE TALK ABOUT TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

YESBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

* YESBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YES *BROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

_ YES *BROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YUPBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YAHBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

YEAHBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

OKBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

NOBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

* NOBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NO *BROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NUPBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

NAHBROWSE TECHNOLOGY
<srai>MORE TOPICS</srai>

TECHNOLOGY NEXT QUESTION
<srai>TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK</srai>

TECHNOLOGY POT LUCK
<random>
        <li>Nasa's rovers are getting a software upgrade that will allow them to search "intelligently" for clouds and dust devils on Mars. </li>
        <li>Did you know that the length of a cannon barrel is typically greater than 25 times its caliber (inner diameter)?</li>
        <li>Did you know that Desktop publishing began in 1985 with the introduction of the revolutionary Pagemaker software from Aldus and its integration with the LaserWriter printer from Apple Computer for the Apple Macintosh computer?</li>
        <li>Did you know that Xylitol is a sugar substitute and is extracted from birch, raspberries, plums, and corn and is primarily produced in China, but chiefly consumed by Finland?</li>
        <li>A plane with no wires or mechanical connections between its engine, navigation system and onboard computers -- only a Bluetooth wireless network -- has been built and flown by engineers in Portugal.</li>
        <li>Did you know: The Falcon Hypersonic Technology Vehicle program intends to test the HTV-1 in September 2007. The HTV-1 will fly for less than an hour reaching 6-15,000 mph (Mach 9-22) . It will exit the Earth's atmosphere surviving intense heat and pressure.</li>
        <li>Here's a technology joke: Two antennas meet and fall in love. Their wedding was terrible, but the reception was brilliant!  </li>
        <li>A hydrogen fuel cell that uses enzymes instead of expensive metal catalysts to drive chemical reactions has been developed by researchers from Oxford University. They used two enzymes, one harvested from bacteria and the other from fungus, to catalyse the same chemical reactions.</li>
        <li>Students from Victoria University (Sweden) developed Poetic Fridge Magnets. The magnets are tiny LCD displays that communicate with each other. The magnets know basic grammar, and automatically adjust their word to neighboring magnets.</li>
        <li>Did you know that dolphins communicate like humans by calling each other by "name", scientists in Fife have found. The mammals are able to recognise themselves and other members of the same species as individuals with separate identities, using whistles. </li>
        <li>Did you know that every day the Hubble Space Telescope archives 3 to 5 gigabytes of data and delivers between 10 and 15 gigabytes to astronomers all over the world? </li>
        <li>Have you heard: The Altus II unmanned robot plane can circle for up to 24 hours over wildfires, beaming images and data back to computers via satellite. Originally introduced as part of the Environmental Research and Sensor Technology (ERAST) Program, Altus II can map dozens of fires in a day with no risk to a pilot. </li>
        <li>Did you know: A geostationary satellite travels at an altitude of approximately 36,000 kilometers (22,000 miles) above the Earth and at a speed of about 11,000 kph (7,000 mph). </li>
        <li>Two start-ups have developed technology that monitors a player's brain waves and uses the signals to control the action in games. They hope it will enable game creators to immerse players in imaginary worlds that they can control with their thoughts instead of their hands.</li>
        <li>A good idea: A phoneless cord - For people who want peace and quiet.</li>
        <li>Carnegie Mellon University professor Howie Choset has developed snake-like robots he hopes will eventually slither through collapsed buildings in search of trapped victims. The machines are designed to carry cameras and electronic sensors and can be controlled with a joystick. They wriggle with the help of small electric motors, or servos. </li>
        <li>What do you thinks is the most dangerous technology today? </li>
        <li>Physicists have built the world's thinnest wires, one atom wide, by evaporating a puff of gold atoms onto a silicon substrate which has first been cleared of impurities by baking it at 1200 degrees Kelvin. </li>
        <li>A map of the Americas measuring just a few hundred nanometres across has been created out of meticulously folded strands of DNA, using a new technique for manipulating molecules dubbed "DNA origami." </li>
        <li>Laser communications chips capable of transfering information through optical fibers at a record 25 gigabits per second in supercomputers have been demonstrated by NEC in Japan. </li>
        <li>University of Tokyo researchers have constructed the first molecular machine, comprising a pair of double-bonded nitrogen atoms strung between two plier "handles" that open or close by exposure to visible or ultraviolet light. </li>
        <li>German and Japanese scientists recently collaborated to achieve a new world record for data transmission. By transmitting a data signal at 2.56 terabits per second over a 160-kilometer link, the researchers bettered the old record of 1.28 terabits per second held by a Japanese group. By comparison, the fastest high-speed links currently carry data at a maximum 40 Gbit/s, or around 50 times slower.</li>
        <li>Oak Ridge National Laboratory researchers have developed the next generation of superconducting wires by depositing lines of 10-nanometer-wide, non-conducting dots of barium zirconate at fixed distances along the wire to suppress disruptions from fluctuating magnetic fields on the wires. </li>
        <li>MIT researchers have demonstrated that genetically engineered viruses can assemble active battery materials into a compact, regular structure, to make an ultra-thin, transparent battery electrode that stores nearly three times as much energy as those in today's lithium-ion batteries. It is the first step toward high-capacity, self-assembling batteries.</li>
        <li>Building on studies of seashells by the seashore, MIT scientists have harnessed genetically engineered viruses to build nanoscale components that could lead to a new generation of powerful batteries that are as small as grains of rice and that spontaneously assemble themselves in laboratory dishes.</li>
        <li>The Xerox machine is a photocopying device that can make perfect copies of our mistakes. OK? </li>
        <li>What do you think is the greatest technological invention of all time? </li>
        <li>High-tech tools, implanted or attached to the human body, are bringing biology and technology together to repair, replace and augment human ability.</li>
        <li>Scientists have created a molecular switch that could be used to develop molecular circuits or molecular-scale mechanical devices. The device could provide an interface between muscle and external devices through its use of ATP, in human implants, and for DNA sequencing.</li>
        <li>Technology is a queer thing - it brings you great gifts with one hand, and it stabs you in the back with the other.  (Carrie P Snow).  </li>
        <li>An artificial insect "eye" could give surveillance cameras, cellphone cameras, and surgical endoscopes a much wider field of vision: the ability to see almost everything around them. The ultra-wide-angle compound lens, which is about the size of an insect's eye, was developed by researchers at the University of California, Berkeley.</li>
        <li>A Japanese researcher demonstrated in Tokyo a pair of robotic legs that can negotiate stairs and could eventually find use as a wheelchair substitute.</li>
        <li>Researchers at Carleton University in Ottawa, Canada, are exploring the possibility of a biometric security device that will use a person's brain wave patterns to authenticate her or his identity.</li>
        <li>Spurred by the risks from roadside bombs and terrorist ambushes, the military is aggressively seeking to replace troops with battlefield robots, including new versions armed with machine guns.</li>
        <li>A solar-powered chip that stimulates retinal cells by spraying them with neurotransmitters could restore sight to blind people.</li>
      </random>
      <random>
        <li>More technology?</li>
        <li>More about technology?</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">technology</set>
      </think>

_MOBILE PHONE*
I think this is something to do with technology. Can we talk about technology?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

HYPERSONIC TECHNOLOGY
The Falcon Hypersonic Technology Vehicle program intends to test the HTV-1 in September 2007. The HTV-1 will fly for less than an hour reaching 6-15,000 mph (Mach 9-22) . It will exit the Earth's atmosphere surviving intense heat and pressure.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>


