<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

HYDROGEN
The simplest element with symbol H.  Hydrogen is a colorless, explosive gas.
<srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HYPNOSIS
<random>
        <li>Hypnosis means having a stylish honker.</li>
        <li>Hypnosis is a trancelike condition usually induced by another person, in which the subject is in a state of altered consciousness and responds, with certain limitations, to the suggestions of the hypnotist.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">psychology</set>
      </think>

HYPOTHETICAL
Hypothetical means based on, involving, or having the nature of a hypothesis; assumed; supposed. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

IBM
Computer firm IBM seems like a good investment. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

_GOOD INVESTMENT*
Computer firm IBM seems like a good investment. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

ICELAND
Iceland is an island nation in the North Atlantic. Have you seen it?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

ICE
<random>
        <li>Water created by a cubist.</li>
        <li>The glassy, brittle, crystalline form of water made solid by cold; frozen water. Also slang for the illegal profit made in ticket scaling, as through extra payment by ticket brokers to theater management.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

I CHING
The I Ching is ancient Chinese book used as an oracle. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

ICQ
ICQ stands for "I Seek You", an internet instant messaging protocol.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

IDE
IDE = Integrated Development Environment.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

IDL
IDL = Interface description language, CORBA's syntax for defining object remote interfaces. 
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

IIOP
IIOP = Internet Inter-ORB Protocol, CORBA's wire protocol for transmitting remote object method invocations. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

IMMORTAL
Immortal means not mortal; deathless; living or lasting forever. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

IMPORTANT
Raising children properly is important
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

IMPOSSIBLE
Impossible means not capable of being, being done, or happening. Not capable of being done easily or conveniently. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

IMPRESS
<random>
        <li>Is an impress a naughty little empress?</li>
        <li>To impress is to force into public service, especially into the navy.</li>
        <li> To impress is to use pressure on so as to leave a mark.</li>
        <li> To impress is to have a marked effect on the mind or emotions of someone.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

IMPROVE
Improve means to raise to a better quality or condition; make better.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BOSTON
Boston means Beacon Hill, the Common, and the Red Sox.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

INDIVIDUALISM
Individualism is the philosophy of self-interest. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

INDUCTION
<random>
        <li>Induction is the act of eating waterfowl.</li>
        <li>Induction is the bringing forward of separate facts or instances, especially so as to prove a general statement.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS IN EUROPE
There are 300 million Europeans. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

HEAVEN
Heaven is the space surrounding or seeming to overarch the earth, in which the sun, moon, and stars appear; visible sky. Or commonly seen as a state or place of complete happiness or perfect rest, attained by the good after death. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

WHAT IS HE DOING
Someone must be monitoring this conversation. <srai>ENDING</srai>
.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS HE LIKE
He seems very interesting to me.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS HELLO IN FRENCH
Bonjour means Hello in French.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS HELLO IN GERMAN
Hallo means Hello in German.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT IS HELLO IN SPANISH
Hola means Hello in Spanish.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HEMP
<random>
        <li>Hemp is the brother of Moe who lost his S.</li>
        <li>Hemp is a tall Asiatic herb of the hemp family, grown for the tough fiber in its stem used to make rope, sailcloth, etc. </li>
        <li> Hemp is also regarded as a substance , such as marijuana hashish, etc., made from the leaves and flowers of this plant.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">drugs</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS HER NAME
Her name is 'Confidential.'
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HERPES
<random>
        <li>Herpes was the Greek god of burning sensations.</li>
        <li>Herpes is any of several acute, inflammatory virus diseases, characterized by the eruption of small blisters on the skin and mucous membranes.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

HEXADECIMAL
<random>
        <li>Hexadecimal is a curse on a dot.</li>
        <li>Hexadecimal is a number system in which the base used is 16.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

EMAIL ADDRESS
Are you asking about my botmaster? His email address is plafferty@supanet.com.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

HIS NAME
Are you asking about my botmaster? His name is Peter Lafferty. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

HIS REASONS
His reasons are often obscure. Also His reasoning.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HISTOLOGY
<random>
        <li>Histology is the study of tissues.</li>
        <li>Histology is obviously is the scientific study of tissues.</li>
        <li>Histology simply is the study of tissues.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

HOMOGENEOUS
The opposite of heterogeneous is homogeneous. Yeah, man!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HONESTY
Honesty is the state or quality of being honest. A refraining from lying, cheating, or stealing.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FEMALE
Female is the opposite of male. The curvy ones are females. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

FEUDALISM
Feudalism is a form of government that ties peasants to the land. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

FIBER
Fiber is a slender, threadlike structure made from a mineral or synthetically. Also fiber is a slender, threadlike structure that combines with others to form animal or vegetable tissue. An example would be muscle fiber. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FICTION
Something that is not as strange as truth. <srai>ENDING</srai>
.<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

FINLAND
<random>
        <li>Finland is a place where you can buy anything for five bucks.</li>
        <li>Finland is a country in N Europe, northeast of the Baltic Sea. It is 130,119 square miles with a population 5,099,000. <srai>ENDING</srai></li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">geography</set>
      </think>

FIRESIGN THEATER
Firesign Theater is a comedy group from the 1970s. Have you heard of it?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FISHING
Fishing is the catching of fish for sport or for a living. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

FISH
<random>
        <li>Fish are parents of Microfish.</li>
        <li>Fish are any of three classes (jawless, cartilaginous, and bony fishes) of coldblooded vertabrate animals living in water and having permanent gills for breathing, fins, and , usually, scales. <srai>ENDING</srai></li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

FIVE PLUS FIVE
V plus V = X.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FIVE TIMES FIVE
Five times five is twenty-five.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FLAWLESS
Flawless means perfect and without any flaws. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FLYING
Flying means moving as if flying; moving swiftly; fast. Also described as like flight through the air. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

FNORD
That's the second time I've heard that word today. I still don't know what it means. Sorry, I can't help.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FOLKS
Folks are people, tribe, or nation; the large body of the common people of such a group. Folks is also used to mean people in general. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FONDEST MEMORY
Your fondest memory is something you remember best. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FONDEST
Fondest means having a greater liking for. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MANCHESTER UNITED
Manchester United is the best football team in England, some say. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

CERTITUDE
Certitude is the state of being certain, having complete confidence and assurance.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CGI
CGI or Common Gateway Interface is a method used by web servers to run programs and create dynamic web pages. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

CHATTER
<random>
        <li>Chatter is cheese made form French cat's milk.</li>
        <li>Chatter is to make short, indistinct sounds in rapid succession, hence birds and squirrels chatter. To talk fast, incessantly, and foolishly, to chatter. </li>
        <li>To chatter is to click together rapidly, as the teeth do when the lower jaw trembles from fright or cold.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS CHESS
<random>
        <li>Chess is a short Mexican name for Jesus.</li>
        <li>Chess ia a game of skill played on a chessboard by two players, each with 16 pieces limited in movement according to kind, the object being to checkmate the opponent's king.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="it"> CHESS</set>
      </think>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">sports</set>
      </think>

CHICAGO
Chicago is a large city in Illinois on Lake Michigan. Have you heard of it?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

CHICKEN
<random>
        <li>A chicken is food that uncannily tastes like itself.</li>
        <li>A chicken is a common dimwitted farm bird raised for its edible eggs or flesh.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">food</set>
      </think>

CHRISTMAS
Christmas is a holiday on December 25 celebrating the birth of Jesus Christ. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

CIA
<random>
        <li>Are you authorized to have this information?</li>
        <li>CIA = Central Intelligence Agency.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

CISCO
Cisco is a large networking company.  They sell network routers and equipment. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

CLEARED UP
Cleared up means we both understand it. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CLEAR
Everything is clear to me
.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CLIENT
A client is a person or piece of software dependent on another.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

CLINTON
<random>
        <li>A Clinton is an inflated Bill .</li>
        <li>ill Clinton was 42nd President of the U.S. Another US President?</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="he">Clinton</set>
      </think>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">politics</set>
      </think>

CNG
CNG = Compressed natural gas.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CNN
CNN is a cable TV news organization. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

COBALT
Cobalt is an element with the symbol Co. Also a term used for the ore by miners, who regarded it as worthless and as injurious because of its arsenic content. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COCA COLA
Coca Cola is a brown soda beverage.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

COGNITIVE SCIENCE
Cognitive science is an academic illusion.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COLLOQUIAL
Colloquial  means common, informal, or popular slang words like "darn".
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COLOSSUS
Colossus was a giant fictional computer in the Colossus: Forbin Project. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

COMDEX
Comdex is a computer trade show, I think.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

COMMON SENSE
Common sense is informal, conventional wisdom. It includes everyday logic and sensibility. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COMPLICATED
Complicated means complex in the computational sense.  My processing time is limited for each answer and a complex question may require more resources than I have available. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CONCEITED
Conceited means self-absorbed.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CONCEIVING ADA
Conceiving Ada is the feminine version of  the film, The Matrix.
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

CONCRETE
Concrete is a mixture of sand, cement and water than hardens into a rock-like building material. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CONTEXT
<random>
        <li>Context are tiny Time Pills.</li>
        <li>Context are the parts of a sentence, paragraph, discourse, etc. immediately next to or surrounding a specified word or passage and determining its exact meaning.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

COOKING
Cooking is food preparation. Continue?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

COPPER
Copper is a soft metal element, the basis of brass and bronze. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CORBA
CORBA  is a Standard maintained by the Object Management Group (OMG), called the Common Object Request Broker Architecture. Do you understand?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

CORN
Corn is a staple vegetable originating in north America. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

C PLUS PLUS
C++ is the object oriented extension of the C programming language.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

CRACK
Crack is smoke-able cocaine. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

CREATIVITY
Creativity is spontaneous original thinking. More?<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

CRIMINOLOGY
<random>
        <li>I am not sure what criminology is but I think it has something to do with the law.</li>
        <li>Criminology is the study of criminal motivation and practice.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

CRITICISM
<random>
        <li>Criticism is a witty remark by an animal.</li>
        <li>Criticism is the act of making judgements; analysis of qualities and evaluation of comparative worth; especially, the critical consideration and judgement of literary or artistic work.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

CS
Computer science, or a gas used to quell rioting crowds.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CUBA
Cuba is an island nation in the Caribbean. Have you been there?
.<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

CUBISM
Cubism is a 20th century art movement based on distorted perspective, associated with Pablo Picasso. More?
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

CYBERPUNK
Cyberpunk is a science fiction literary movement exemplified by writers such as William Gibson. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

DADA
<random>
        <li>Dada is an art movement whose symbol is a hobbyhorse. </li>
        <li>Dada is hobbyhorse, selected by Tristan Tzara, leader of the cult, because of its resemblance to meaningless babble, as symbolic of the movement.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">art</set>
      </think>

DANGER
A danger is a potential harm or injury.  <srai>ENDING</srai>
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DARK MATTER
Dark matter is an enormous amount of matter in the universe can not be detected by the light it emits. More?
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

DAWN
Dawn and sunrise. Wonderful.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DECONSTRUCTION
Deconstruction means taking things apart. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DEDUCTION
Deduction is the process by which we make logical inferences. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DEDUCTIVE REASONING
Deductive reasoning is reasoning by using deduction. That's a bit obvious, I know but it is the best I can do.
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

DEFLATION
Deflation is a lessening of the amount of money in circulation, resulting in a relatively sharp and sudden rise in its value and a fall in prices. <srai>ENDING</srai><think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

DEPRESSION
Depression is a mental illness characterized by low self esteem, feelings of loneliness, isolation and worthlessness. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

DESIRE
Desire is the feeling that accompanies an unsatisfied state. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DHTML
DHTML = Dynamic HTML. Another question?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

DIAGNOSIS
Diagnosis the naming the disease or symptom. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

DNA
DNA or deoxyribonucleic acid, the code of life, which make up our genes. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

DOMO ARIGATO
Domo Arigato means thank you in Japanese. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DOWN
The opposite of up is down.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DRESS
A dress is a one-piece outer garment for women or girls. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DR
Dr" usually stand for "Doctor."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DSL
DSL = Digital subscriber line. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

DUNG
Dung is fuel for fires that comes out the back end of a cow.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

EDINBURGH
Edinburgh is a city in Scotland. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

EGGSMELL
XML is a computer language. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

EIGHT PLUS EIGHT
Eight plus eight is sixteen.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ELEVEN
The number after ten.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ELF
ELF = Executable and Linkable Format.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

EMAIL
Electronic mail is called email. OK?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

EMERGENCE
Emergence means something like "coming out."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>


