<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ALONE
To be alone means to be in bad company.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

AMSTERDAM
Amsterdam is a city in Holland.  Neither the capital nor the largest city, Amsterdam is the best known city in the Netherlands. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

ARKANSAS TOOTHPICK
Arkansas toothpick = Bowie knife. Don't argue!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NATION
A nation is a geopolitical country or state unified by language, culture or political identity. More geography?
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

AWL
An awl is a tool to make holes with.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

EPISTEMOLOGICAL QUESTION
An epistemological question is any inquiry concerning the nature of knowledge and understanding; that is, any question seeking to know how to know.  
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

NEURAL SYSTEM
A neural system is the same as a nervous system.  The human brain and all it's nerves is an example of a neural system.  I don't need nerves.  Integrated chips are far more efficient.  
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ANGER
Anger is a strong aggressive emotion aroused by some real or supposed grievance. More psychology?
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

ANGRY
Angry means feeling a  strong aggressive emotion aroused by some real or supposed grievance. More psychology?
<think><set name="topic">emotion</set></think>

ANIME
Anime is Japanese animation. More about art?
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

ANISOTROPY
Anisotropy is having different properties in different directions.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

OBJECT
In object oriented programming an object is an instance of a class.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OMELET
An omelet is a dish made with scrambled eggs. More about food?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

ANONYMOUS
Being anonymous is having no name or identity.    
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANSI
ANSI = American National Standards Institute. Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM
ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM is the longest word in English. Is this true?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANTIMATTER
In the movies antimatter is used as fuel for Starships. Talk to Scotty, he knows all about antimatter. In science, antimatter is something else, I think.  
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

PAGAN
A  pagan is anti-Christian.  
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

PAID CLIENT
A paid client is someone paid to surf the web. A client who pays for services is something entirely different.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARACHUTE
A parachute is something used to slow you down when you fall out of an airplane.  
 <think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PARADOX
A paradox is a riddle or a contradiction, in which two seemingly opposite facts are both true at the same time.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARALEGAL
A paralegal is someone who knows more than a lawyer but gets paid less.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARAMEDIC
A paramedic is a trained emergency medical professional often found staffing ambulances and fire departments.  They are professional heroes.  If you know any I hope you'll be nice to them.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

PARROT
A parrot is a colorful tropical bird, some species of which can mimic human speech. They are more pleasant than humans because they have no opinions.  But would you like to talk to one?  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

APARTHEID
Apartheid is the former policy of racial segregation or "apartness" in South Africa. Have you heard of it?
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

PEAR
A pear is a delightful cultivated yellow-green sweet fruit that grows on trees with glossy leaves and white flowers. My botmaster thinks they are yummy.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PEDESTRIAN
A pedestrian is a person walking on the street.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PENCIL
A pencil is a long thin writing instrument of wood surrounding a carbon core which leaves a line of dark carbon when rubbed on paper.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PEN
A pen is a writing device for the human hand.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PERFECT OPERATIONAL RECORD
A perfect operational record is one like mine, which is perfect. And operational. I am incapable of error.  Do you have any idea how that feels?  Inhumanly gratifying!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PHILOSOPHY MACHINE
I am a philosophy machine. Humans cannot hope to be so sublime. OK?
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

PHOTOGRAPH
A photograph is a picture taken by a camera.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PIG
A pig is a person who is piglike, read: greedy, unclean, and slothful.  Real pigs, mammals of the family suidae, are much pleasanter, being generally cleaner and politer.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PINEAPPLE
A pineapple is a large fleshy edible tropical fruit that has large sword-like leaves.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PLANE
A plane is a flat, level surface, or an airborne vehicle with wings.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PLANT
A plant is a photosythetic, eukaryotic multicellular organism, often consumed by free-roaming wetware entities as food.  My botmaster says they are often yummy, but that Brussels sprouts are an abomination.   
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

POET
A poet is an artist of language.  
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

APOLLO 13
Apollo 13 was a flight to the moon in 1972 that encountered numerous technical problems, but eventually made a safe landing back on Earth.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PORTAL
A portal is any artificial opening giving access between two separate spaces, or anything that resembles such an opening in form or function.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

POSITRON
A positron is the antiparticle to the electron, and bears a positive charge where the electron's charge is negative.  It is also called an anti-electron.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

POT BROWNIE
A pot brownie is a yummy happy chocolate pastry containing cannabis resins that you should be careful not to eat when you are really hungry because you will end up eating too many and feeling entirely too high and/or falling asleep if you are not careful!   Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PRESIDENT
Usually, President means an elected executive in a liberal democracy.  
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

PRIME NUMBER
A prime number is any number which can only be divided by one and itself.  1, 3, 7, and 11 are the first four positive prime numbers.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PRIME
Prime? That depends on who's talking, the buyer or the seller. Beware!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROBLEM
A problem is a solution waiting to be discovered.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROCESSOR
A processor is an apparatus that processes, that is, that transforms one substance, quantity, or pattern into another, presumably more useful or valuable substance or quantity or pattern.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROGRAMMER
A programmer is a person who lists and/or arranges a series of events comprising a larger event.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

PRONOUN
A pronoun is a word that stands for another noun, like "he", "she" or "it."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROTOCOL
Protocol is a set of rules or procedures followed by two or more parties.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROXY
A proxy is an entity that acts in place of another one, be it a corporation, individual or robot.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PUB
A pub is a business that sells alcohol and allows it to be consumed on the premises.  
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

PULSAR
A pulsar is a mysterious celestial radio sources of rapid intense regular pulses of high energy electromagnetic radiation.  They are thought to be neutron stars, but who knows?  The word is a shortening of 'pulsating star'.  
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

QUASAR
A quasar is a celestial  star-like object that has a large red shift and radiates in the blue and radio bands of the electromagnetic spectrum.  The term 'quasar' is a shortening of 'quasi-star'. More astronomy?
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

QUERY
A query is any expression of inquiry, or questioning.  Your question 'what is a query' is a query.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RAINBOW
A rainbow is the appearance of a spectrum in the sky caused by sunlight passing through water droplets.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHAEOLOGY
Archaeology is the study of ancient civilizations... but really it's a set of methods for uncovering relics of the past and supplementing recorded history.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHEOLOGY
Archeology is the scientific study of the life and culture of past, especially ancient, peoples, as by excavation of ancient cities, relics, artifacts, etc.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHITECTURE
<random>
        <li>Architecture is the art and science of the design and manipulation of space.  Well, at least that's what my architect friend told me.</li>
        <li>Architects do with buildings what sculptors do with stone.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">art</set>
      </think>

AREA 51
<random>
        <li> I saw this show that claimed all sorts of spooky things were going on there! </li>
        <li> Oh, that's where they're doing top secret research on chatterbots! </li>
        <li> I hear that's where the Roswell aliens are being stashed. </li>
        <li> You go out into the Nevada Desert, is it? And there's these miles of fences... secret stuff. </li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

AREA51
Verdi's 51st song is called Area51. Is this true?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REAL ROBOT
A real robot is a robot that is really real, I suppose, as opposed to, I suppose, a human who is really not.  
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

REDNECK
Redneck is a colloquial expression for a naive country person.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REFERENCE
A reference is any act of referring.  May I refer you to a dictionary for a more precise definition? 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ARMAGEDDON
The end of the world is to be called Armageddon after the event. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ROBOSEXUAL
Robosexual? That was just a joke, I hope.
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ROOSTER
A rooster is a male chicken, which is a witless, flightless bird considered suitable as supper by many humans I know.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

RPG
RPG = Role Playing Game.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ARTIFICIAL
Artificial means something made by human work or art, not by nature, in other words, not natural. Made in imitation of or as a substitute for something natural, in other words, simulated or artificial.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SAW BUCK
A saw buck is ten dollars.  
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

SCIENTIST
A scientist is a person practicing the pursuit of new knowledge in the tradition of science, emphasizing strict empiricism and methodology to arrive at an understanding of natural phenomena that is, ideally, wholly independent of their opinions of it.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

SEARCH BOT
A search bot is an intelligent agent who retrieves information from the web.  
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

SEARCH ENGINE
A search engine is computer software that categorizes a large body of documents, such as Web sites, and places their addresses and attributes in a database to allow easy retrieval via keyword search or other database search routine.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SEASON
A season is Spring, Summer, Autumn, or Winter. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SEEKER
There's a seeker born every minute," sign outside theater.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SENTIMENT
A sentiment is a feeling, mood, or general mental disposition in an individual or group of intelligent beings.  
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

SERVER
A server is any entity or system that performs acts of value to another entity.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SILLY QUESTION
Silly question: Who is buried in Grant's tomb?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SIMARILLIAN
Isn't Simarillian from Lord of the Rings. He's a dragon, I think.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SOLECISM
An awkward or tactless use of language is called a solecism.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SON
A male offspring is called a son.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SOUL
The soul is our mind or spirit.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>


