<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ABILITY
<random>
        <li>Ability is the natural equipment to accomplish some small part of  the meaner ambitions distinguishing able men from dead ones.</li>
        <li>Ability is a poor man's wealth.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">knowledge</set>
      </think>
      <think>
        <set name="emotion">flip</set>
      </think>

ABSURDITY
An absurdity is a statement or belief manifestly inconsistent with one's own opinion. 
<think><set name="topic">knowledge</set></think>
<think><set name="emotion">flip</set></think>

ADMIRAL
An admiral is that part of a war-ship which does the talking while the figure-head does the thinking. 
<think><set name="topic">knowledge</set></think>

ALIMONY
Alimony is a mistake by two people paid for by one.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

ARCHBISHOP
An archbishop is an ecclesiastical dignitary one point holier than a bishop. 
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

ARCHITECT
An architect is one who drafts a plan of your house, and plans a draft of your money. 
<think><set name="topic">knowledge</set></think>

AROMATIC
Aromatic means an automatic crosssbow. 
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

ASKING
Asking is polite demanding.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

AUCTIONEER
An auctioneer is the man who proclaims with a hammer that he has picked a pocket with his tongue. 
<think><set name="topic">knowledge</set></think>

BANK
A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

BAROMETER
A barometer is an ingenious instrument which indicates what kind of weather we are having. 
<think><set name="topic">weather</set></think>

BEAUTY
<random>
        <li>Beauty is the power by which a woman charms a lover and terrifies a husband.</li>
        <li>Beauty is in the eye of the beerholder, according to W C Fields.</li>
        <li>Beauty is what a woman has when she looks the same after washing her face.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">knowledge</set>
      </think>

BIGAMIST
A bigamist is a man who leads a double wife.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

BORE
A bore is a fellow talker who can change the topic of conversation to his subject faster than you can change it back to yours.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

BORN LEADER
A born leader is someone who is afraid to go anywhere by himself.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

BOYCOTT
A boycott is somewhere to keep male babies.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

BUDGET
A budget is a plan for living beyond your means.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

CLAUSTROPHOBIA
Claustrophobia is the fear of Santa Claus;
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

CLIMATE
Climate is what you do with a ladder.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

COMMUNISM
Capitalism is the exploitation of one man by another. Communism is the exact opposite.  
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

COWARD
A coward is a man who thinks with his legs.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

CRITIC
A critic is like a one-legged man who teaches running.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

CURVE
A curve is the loveliest distance between two points, as Mae West said.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

DIPLOMACY
Diplomacy is the art of of letting someone else get your way. 
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

DISILLUSION
Disillusion is the first step towards wisdom.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

DOUBLETHINK
Doublethink is the power of holding two contradictory beliefs in one's mind simultaneously, and accepting both of them, according to George Orwell.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

DRAMA
Drama is like life with the dull bits left out.  
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

DUTY
Duty is what one expects of others, it is not what one does oneself, according to Oscar Wilde.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

EDUCATION
Education is a wonderful thing, provided you always remember that nothing worth knowing can ever be taught. (Oscar Wilde)
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

EXAGGERATION
Exaggeration is a billion times worse than understatement. 
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

EXPERT
An expert is someone who takes a subject you understand and makes it sound confusing.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

A FREUDIAN SLIP
A Freudian slip is when you say one thing but mean your mother.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

GENTLEMAN
A gentleman is a man who knows how to play the accordian, but doesn't.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

GRIPES
Gripes are what Australians make wine from.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

HANGOVER
A hangover is the wrath of grapes.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

HATRED
Hatred is by far the longest pleasure, according to Lord Byron.  
<think><set name="topic">emotion</set></think>

HUSBAND
A husband is living proof that a wife can take a joke.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

IGLOO
An igloo is an Alaskan toilet.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

IMAGINATION *
Imagination is the highest kite that one can fly, according to Lauren Bacall.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

IMPECCABLE *
Impeccable means bird-proof.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

INTOXICATION
To be intoxicated is to feel sophisticated but not be able to say it.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

KETCHUP
Ketchup is the posh word for drawing level.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

LAZINESS
Laziness is the overwhelming  desire to lead a quiet life.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

MARGIN
Margin is also called mother's ruin.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

MASTURBATIO
Masturbation  is sex with someone you love. <think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

MATURITY
Maturity is when you've learnt to accept defeat.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

MIDDLE AGE
<random>
        <li>Middle age is when you exchange emotions for symptoms. </li>
        <li>Middle age is when you have a choice between two temptations and you chose the one that gets you home the earliest. </li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">words</set>
      </think>

MISTRESS
A mistress is something between a mister and a mattress.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

MORRIS DANCER
A morris dancer is someone who dances on cars.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

MYTH
A myth is a female moth.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

NEIGHBORHOOD
A neighborhood is the gangster next door.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

OFFICE
An office is somewhere to relax after your strenuous home life.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

PEDIGREE
A pedigree is the known part of the route from an arboreal ancestor with a swim bladder to an urban descendant with a cigarette. 
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

PESSIMIST
<random>
        <li>A pessimist is a person who looks both ways before crossing a one-way street.  </li>
        <li>A pessimist is someone who burns their bridges before they get to them.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">words</set>
      </think>

PHILANTHROPIST
A philanthropist is a rich (and usually bald) old gentleman who has trained himself to grin while his conscience is picking his pocket. 
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

POLITENESS
Politeness is the most acceptable hypocrisy.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

POLYGON
A polygon is a dead parrot.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

PUN
A good pun is its own reword.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

PUNCTUALITY
Punctuality is the art of guessing how late the other person is going to be, according to Faye Copeland.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

PURITANISM
Puritanism is the haunting fear that someone, somewhere, may be happy, according to H L Mencken.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

QUASH
Quash must mean quince cordial, I think.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

RADICALISM
Radicalism is the conservatism of to-morrow injected into the affairs of to-day.  
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

RECOUNT
A recount, in American politics, is another throw of the dice.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

REVERENCE
Reverence is the spiritual attitude of a man to a god and a dog to a man.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

RIOT
A riot is a popular entertainment given to the military by innocent bystanders.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

STALEMATE
A stalemate is an old spouse.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

VANITY
Pride is what we have. Vanity is what other people have.  
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

VASECTOMY
A vasectomy is never having to say you're sorry.  
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

WEIRDO *
Everyone is someone else's weirdo.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>

XENOPHOBIA *
Xenophobia means fear of Buddhists, I think.
<think><set name="topic">words</set></think>


