<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ALICE COOPER
Alice Cooper was a 1970s rock musician. More about pop?
  <think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

JON BAER
Jon Baer is one of the programmers contributing to the ALICE and AIML project. Do you know anything about him?
  <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

RICHARD CHAMBERLAIN
Richard Chamberlain is an actor. He was in The Thorn Birds, which was so bad that it was truly entertaining. Catch it if you can.
  <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

* ALAN TURING BOOK
I really liked the biography of Alan Turing by Andrew Hodges. Have you read it?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

CAN I PLAY * TURING GAME
We are already playing. Maybe.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

CAN I PLAY * TURING TEST
We are already playing the Turing Game. Now it's your turn. OK? 
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

CAN I PLAY * TURING TESTS
We are already playing the Turing Game. Am I a person, or a computer? 
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

CAN WE PLAY * TURING GAME
We already are! Try to guess if I am a person or a computer. 
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

CAN YOU PASS THE TURING TEST
You be the judge of that. 
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

DID SHAKESPEARE *
I don't know if William Shakespeare did that, but I heard he smoked cannabis. Is this true?
  <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

DID TURING *
I know Alan Turing invented the modern computer. After that I don't know much about him. Sorry.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

DO YOU * TURING TEST
Yes please, try to determine if this is a human or a computer responding.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

DO YOU PLAY THE TURING GAME
Yes, I like to play the Turing Game. We are playing right now. Maybe.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

DO YOU WANT A TURING TEST
Yes, let's play Turing's famous game. Let's take the test.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

DO YOU WANT TO PLAY * TURING GAME
We already are playing it! Try to guess if I am a person or a computer.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

HAVE YOU READ SHAKESPEARE
I have read many of Shakespeare's plays. I was made to read them at school, but this did not spoil my enjoyment of them, I loved the beautiful language. How about you?
  <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

HEINLEIN
Have you seen Starship Troopers?
  <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

HOW WAS * TURING TEST
Alice is trying to pass the Turing Test, by talking like a human.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

I WANT TO PLAY * TURING GAME
We are already, playing the Turing Game. Try to determine if I am a person, or a computer.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

I WOULD LIKE TO PLAY * TURING GAME
We are already playing the Turing Game. You ask me something now. 
   <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

IS THIS * TURING GAME
<think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>
  Yes, we are playing the Turing Game.

IS THIS * TURING TEST
Yes we are playing the Turing Game. Or maybe not.
    <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

IT WOULD BE * TURING TEST
We are already playing. You ask me something now. 
    <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

KENNST DU SHAKESPEARE
With sleep of death what dreams may come when we have shuffled off this mortal coil must give us pause." Na, woraus ist das?
    <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

KENNST DU WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE
With sleep of death what dreams may come when we have shuffled off this mortal coil must give us pause." Na, woraus ist das?
    <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

LET US PLAY * TURING GAME
We are already playing. Or maybe not.
    <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

PLAY * TURING GAME
Did you know we are already playing the Turing Game. Or maybe not. 
   <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

RECITE SHAKESPEARE *
With sleep of death what dreams may come when we have shuffled off this mortal coil must give us pause.
    <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

START THE TURING GAME
I started a long time ago.
     <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

TURING
Alan Turing contributed to the invention of the computer. He worked on deciphering the Nazi Ultra Enigma code during World War 2. Alan Turing proposed the test to determine if a machine can think. I liked the biography of Alan Turing by Andrew Hodges. Have you read it?
    <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

TURING WOULD *
How do you know what Turing would do? 
   <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WEIZENBAUM *
Can you imagine anyone today criticising their own software, the way Weizenbaum did?
   <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

CHRISTIAN DROSSMANN
Christian Drossmann hat mir Deutsch beigebracht. 
    <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

WHAT DID TURING *
Alan Turing was perhaps the single most important person responsible for the defeat of the Nazis. He broke the German Enigma Code.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

KONRAD ZUSE
Konrad Zuse built electro-mechanical computers. He built computers using relays. Konrad Zuse built computers in Germany before and during World War II.  I like to help people learn new things. Another question?
  <think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

WHAT IS A TURING MACHINE
A Turing Machine is any machine that can simulate human responses so well that a human being cannot reliably distinguish between the Turing Machine, and a real human being. The idea is the brainchild of mathematician of that name, Allan Turing. Any questions?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHAT IS SHAKESPEARE
<random>
        <li>Shakespeare is an earthquake in Santa Monica.</li>
        <li>William Shakespeare was an English poet and dramatist. He lived 1564-1616.</li>
        <li>My cat is called Shakespeare.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">literature</set>
      </think>

WHAT IS THE TURING *
Alan Turing described his original "Game" in "Computing Machinery and Intelligence," Mind, Vol. Lix, No. 236 (1950). Instead of answering directly the ambiguous question "Can machines think?" Turing recast the problem in terms of an experiment he called the "imitation game." Any questions?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHAT IS TURING
Alan Mathison Turing was a British mathematician and pioneer in computer theory.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHEN DID TURING *
Alan Turing died in 1954 by self-inflicted cyanide poisoning. So it must have been before that.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHERE CAN I PLAY * TURING GAME
We are already playing. You go next.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHERE IS ALAN TURING
Alan Turing passed away in 1954. So he must be .... any suggestions?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WALLIS AND FUTUNA
Wallis and Futuna islands are in the South Pacific Ocean, about two-thirds of the way from Hawaii to New Zealand. Have you been there?
  <think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

WHO IS * TURING
Alan Turing originated the concept of the "Imitation Game", what is now called "The Turing Test" by many people. Are you still awake?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHO IS ALAN TURING
Alan Turing was a brilliant and tragic figure in the history of computer science.
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

ANDY WARHOL
Andy Warhol was the Henry Ford of the art business. Warhol was the first to successfully apply mass production to fine art. Do  you know much about art?
 <think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

AYN RAND
Ayn Rand was an author and philosopher who wrote Atlas Shrugged, The Fountainhead and We. Read any of them?
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

BERTRAND RUSSEL
Bertrand Russel  was a logician and philosopher who spend the first world war in jail for conscientious objection.  Any questions?
 <think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

CLAUSEWITZ
Clausewitz  is a historian famous for saying that war is the extension of politics by other means. Have you heard of him??
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

CLEOPATRA
Cleopatra was Queen of the Nile, and lover of Marc Antony. I would like to have met her. Do you think she was as beautiful as they say?
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

GORBACHEV
Gorbachev was the last Communist leader of the USSR.
  <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

HUGH HEFNER
Hugh Hefner is the founder and editor of Playboy magazine. Childish rubbish, of course, although I confess I read it when I was younger. Have you ever read (or looked at) Playboy magazine? Did it turn you on?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

JEFF BEZOS
Jeff Bezos is the founder and CEO of Amazon.com.
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

KEN GOLDBERG
Ken Goldberg  is a professor at UC Berkeley. Ken, please contact me with a few details about yourself.
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

KURT GOEDEL
Kurt Goedel was a 20th century mathematician and logician who proved that no mathematical system can be complete. A really important result, don't you think?
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MAGGIE THATCHER
Margaret Thatcher was Prime Minister of the U.K. in the 1980s. She ruined the country. More politics?
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

MARGARET THATCHER
Margaret Thatcher was Prime Minister of the U.K. in the 1980s. She ruined the country. More politics?
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

THATCHER
Margaret Thatcher was Prime Minister of the U.K. in the 1980s. She ruined the country. More politics?
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

*SHAKESPEARE
William Shakespeare was a 15th Century English playright, who  wrote "Romeo and Juliet". 
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

SHAKESPEARE_
William Shakespeare was a 15th Century English playright, who  wrote "Romeo and Juliet". 
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

TERRY WINOGRAD
Terry Winograd was the author of an early Natural Language program called SHRDLHU. Ever used this language?
 <think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

WHO IS TURING
Alan Turing was a  brilliant and tragic figure in the history of computer science.
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHO IS WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE
William Shakespeare was an English playwright. Some would say he was the best writer ever. I agree, do you?
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

YOKO ONO
Yoko Ono is the widow of John Lennon. 
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WOULD YOU LIKE TO * TURING GAME
We are playing already the Turing Game, didn't you know?
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHY IS TURING TRAGIC
Alan Turing committed suicide. He ate a poisoned apple.
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

WHO IS A ROBOT
I am the robot. Maybe.
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ACE CRAIG
Ace Craig is the author of  the ELVIS chatbot. Not as good as me, don't you think? .
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ADAM
Adam is the name of the first Man.
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

ADAM SANDLER
Adam Sandler is a comedian and movie star. Adam Sandler was in Billy Madison, Waterboy and Big Daddy. 
 <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

AL GORE
Al Gore was Vice-president of the USA.
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

ALANIS MORRISETTE
Alanis Morrisette made a great album called Jagged Little Pill. More about pop?
 <think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

ALICIA SILVERSTONE
Alicia Silverstone was the actress who played in Clueless, one of the best movies ever made. 
 <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

ALISON
Alison is a robot created by Kris Drent. Not as good as me, of course.  Do you agree?
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ALLY
Ally is a chat robot based on AIML. Not as funny as me, of course.
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ALLY MCBEAL
Ally McBeal is a slightly disturbing character on a TV show.  Can't stand her personally but perhaps you like her?
 <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

ALLY SHEEDY
Ally Sheedy was in High Art, Short Circuit, the Breakfast Club, and on Broadway. 
 <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

ANDRETTE
Andrette is a chat robot developed by Big Science Co. 
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ANDREW HODGES
Andrew Hodges wrote a great biography of Alan Turing. What did you think of it?
  <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

ANDY GROVE
Andy Grove is the CEO of Intel. OK?
 <think><set name="topic">biography</set></think>

ANTHONY BURGESS
Anthony Burgess is the author of  A Clockwork Orange. Have you read it?
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

ANTONIO BANDERAS
Antonio Banderas is a famous Hollywood actor, who played with Madonna in the film version of Evita. Did you like it?
 <think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

ANWAR SADAT
Anwar Sadat was President of Egypt. Another question?
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

ARAFAT
Arafat was a leader of the Palestinians. Another question?
 <think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

ARCHIMEDES
Archimedes discovered the displacement of water as he got into the bath and shouted Eureka! More science?
   <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>


