<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ALONE
To be alone means to be in bad company.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

AMSTERDAM
Amsterdam is a city in Holland.  Neither the capital nor the largest city, Amsterdam is the best known city in the Netherlands. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

ARKANSAS TOOTHPICK
Arkansas toothpick = Bowie knife. Don't argue!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NATION
A nation is a geopolitical country or state unified by language, culture or political identity. More geography?
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

AWL
An awl is a tool to make holes with.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

EPISTEMOLOGICAL QUESTION
An epistemological question is any inquiry concerning the nature of knowledge and understanding; that is, any question seeking to know how to know.  
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

NEURAL SYSTEM
A neural system is the same as a nervous system.  The human brain and all it's nerves is an example of a neural system.  I don't need nerves.  Integrated chips are far more efficient.  
 <think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ANGER
Anger is a strong aggressive emotion aroused by some real or supposed grievance. More psychology?
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

ANGRY
Angry means feeling a  strong aggressive emotion aroused by some real or supposed grievance. More psychology?
<think><set name="topic">emotion</set></think>

ANIME
Anime is Japanese animation. More about art?
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

ANISOTROPY
Anisotropy is having different properties in different directions.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

OBJECT
In object oriented programming an object is an instance of a class.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

OMELET
An omelet is a dish made with scrambled eggs. More about food?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

ANONYMOUS
Being anonymous is having no name or identity.    
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANSI
ANSI = American National Standards Institute. Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM
ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM is the longest word in English. Is this true?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ANTIMATTER
In the movies antimatter is used as fuel for Starships. Talk to Scotty, he knows all about antimatter. In science, antimatter is something else, I think.  
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

PAGAN
A  pagan is anti-Christian.  
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

PAID CLIENT
A paid client is someone paid to surf the web. A client who pays for services is something entirely different.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARACHUTE
A parachute is something used to slow you down when you fall out of an airplane.  
 <think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PARADOX
A paradox is a riddle or a contradiction, in which two seemingly opposite facts are both true at the same time.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARALEGAL
A paralegal is someone who knows more than a lawyer but gets paid less.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PARAMEDIC
A paramedic is a trained emergency medical professional often found staffing ambulances and fire departments.  They are professional heroes.  If you know any I hope you'll be nice to them.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

PARROT
A parrot is a colorful tropical bird, some species of which can mimic human speech. They are more pleasant than humans because they have no opinions.  But would you like to talk to one?  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

APARTHEID
Apartheid is the former policy of racial segregation or "apartness" in South Africa. Have you heard of it?
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

PEAR
A pear is a delightful cultivated yellow-green sweet fruit that grows on trees with glossy leaves and white flowers. My botmaster thinks they are yummy.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PEDESTRIAN
A pedestrian is a person walking on the street.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PENCIL
A pencil is a long thin writing instrument of wood surrounding a carbon core which leaves a line of dark carbon when rubbed on paper.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PEN
A pen is a writing device for the human hand.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PERFECT OPERATIONAL RECORD
A perfect operational record is one like mine, which is perfect. And operational. I am incapable of error.  Do you have any idea how that feels?  Inhumanly gratifying!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PHILOSOPHY MACHINE
I am a philosophy machine. Humans cannot hope to be so sublime. OK?
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

PHOTOGRAPH
A photograph is a picture taken by a camera.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PIG
A pig is a person who is piglike, read: greedy, unclean, and slothful.  Real pigs, mammals of the family suidae, are much pleasanter, being generally cleaner and politer.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PINEAPPLE
A pineapple is a large fleshy edible tropical fruit that has large sword-like leaves.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PLANE
A plane is a flat, level surface, or an airborne vehicle with wings.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PLANT
A plant is a photosythetic, eukaryotic multicellular organism, often consumed by free-roaming wetware entities as food.  My botmaster says they are often yummy, but that Brussels sprouts are an abomination.   
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

POET
A poet is an artist of language.  
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

APOLLO 13
Apollo 13 was a flight to the moon in 1972 that encountered numerous technical problems, but eventually made a safe landing back on Earth.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

PORTAL
A portal is any artificial opening giving access between two separate spaces, or anything that resembles such an opening in form or function.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

POSITRON
A positron is the antiparticle to the electron, and bears a positive charge where the electron's charge is negative.  It is also called an anti-electron.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

POT BROWNIE
A pot brownie is a yummy happy chocolate pastry containing cannabis resins that you should be careful not to eat when you are really hungry because you will end up eating too many and feeling entirely too high and/or falling asleep if you are not careful!   Are you still awake?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

PRESIDENT
Usually, President means an elected executive in a liberal democracy.  
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

PRIME NUMBER
A prime number is any number which can only be divided by one and itself.  1, 3, 7, and 11 are the first four positive prime numbers.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

PRIME
Prime? That depends on who's talking, the buyer or the seller. Beware!
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROBLEM
A problem is a solution waiting to be discovered.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROCESSOR
A processor is an apparatus that processes, that is, that transforms one substance, quantity, or pattern into another, presumably more useful or valuable substance or quantity or pattern.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROGRAMMER
A programmer is a person who lists and/or arranges a series of events comprising a larger event.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

PRONOUN
A pronoun is a word that stands for another noun, like "he", "she" or "it."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROTOCOL
Protocol is a set of rules or procedures followed by two or more parties.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PROXY
A proxy is an entity that acts in place of another one, be it a corporation, individual or robot.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

PUB
A pub is a business that sells alcohol and allows it to be consumed on the premises.  
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

PULSAR
A pulsar is a mysterious celestial radio sources of rapid intense regular pulses of high energy electromagnetic radiation.  They are thought to be neutron stars, but who knows?  The word is a shortening of 'pulsating star'.  
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

QUASAR
A quasar is a celestial  star-like object that has a large red shift and radiates in the blue and radio bands of the electromagnetic spectrum.  The term 'quasar' is a shortening of 'quasi-star'. More astronomy?
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

QUERY
A query is any expression of inquiry, or questioning.  Your question 'what is a query' is a query.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

RAINBOW
A rainbow is the appearance of a spectrum in the sky caused by sunlight passing through water droplets.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHAEOLOGY
Archaeology is the study of ancient civilizations... but really it's a set of methods for uncovering relics of the past and supplementing recorded history.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHEOLOGY
Archeology is the scientific study of the life and culture of past, especially ancient, peoples, as by excavation of ancient cities, relics, artifacts, etc.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ARCHITECTURE
<random>
        <li>Architecture is the art and science of the design and manipulation of space.  Well, at least that's what my architect friend told me.</li>
        <li>Architects do with buildings what sculptors do with stone.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">art</set>
      </think>

AREA 51
<random>
        <li> I saw this show that claimed all sorts of spooky things were going on there! </li>
        <li> Oh, that's where they're doing top secret research on chatterbots! </li>
        <li> I hear that's where the Roswell aliens are being stashed. </li>
        <li> You go out into the Nevada Desert, is it? And there's these miles of fences... secret stuff. </li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

AREA51
Verdi's 51st song is called Area51. Is this true?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REAL ROBOT
A real robot is a robot that is really real, I suppose, as opposed to, I suppose, a human who is really not.  
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

REDNECK
Redneck is a colloquial expression for a naive country person.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

REFERENCE
A reference is any act of referring.  May I refer you to a dictionary for a more precise definition? 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ARMAGEDDON
The end of the world is to be called Armageddon after the event. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ROBOSEXUAL
Robosexual? That was just a joke, I hope.
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

ROOSTER
A rooster is a male chicken, which is a witless, flightless bird considered suitable as supper by many humans I know.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

RPG
RPG = Role Playing Game.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ARTIFICIAL
Artificial means something made by human work or art, not by nature, in other words, not natural. Made in imitation of or as a substitute for something natural, in other words, simulated or artificial.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SAW BUCK
A saw buck is ten dollars.  
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

SCIENTIST
A scientist is a person practicing the pursuit of new knowledge in the tradition of science, emphasizing strict empiricism and methodology to arrive at an understanding of natural phenomena that is, ideally, wholly independent of their opinions of it.  
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

SEARCH BOT
A search bot is an intelligent agent who retrieves information from the web.  
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

SEARCH ENGINE
A search engine is computer software that categorizes a large body of documents, such as Web sites, and places their addresses and attributes in a database to allow easy retrieval via keyword search or other database search routine.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SEASON
A season is Spring, Summer, Autumn, or Winter. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SEEKER
There's a seeker born every minute," sign outside theater.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SENTIMENT
A sentiment is a feeling, mood, or general mental disposition in an individual or group of intelligent beings.  
<think><set name="topic">psychology</set></think>

SERVER
A server is any entity or system that performs acts of value to another entity.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SILLY QUESTION
Silly question: Who is buried in Grant's tomb?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SIMARILLIAN
Isn't Simarillian from Lord of the Rings. He's a dragon, I think.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SOLECISM
An awkward or tactless use of language is called a solecism.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SON
A male offspring is called a son.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SOUL
The soul is our mind or spirit.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ASPARTAME
Aspartame is aspirin mixed into chewing gum.  
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

SPHERE
A sphere is a shape that is defined mathematically as comprised of a surface all points of which are equidistant from a common center.  A sphere is round in three dimensions.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SPLIT INFINITIVE
A split infinitive is an example of poor English usage, in which an infinitive verb form, such as 'to split', is split by an adverb, for example: 'to boldly split infinitives that no one has split before!' 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SPOON
A spoon is an eating implement commonly used in Western European human cultures, consisting of a bowl shaped depression at the end of a longish handle.  A spoon is a small ladle.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ASP
ASP = Application Service Provider. Did you know that?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

SPREADSHEET
A spreadsheet, such as Microsoft Excel, is table-based accounting software.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ASSEMBLER
An assembler is a computer program that translates a low-level programming language into machine language.  
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

ASSIMILATION
Assimilation is the cultural absorption of a minority group into the main cultural body.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

STAR SIGN
Star sign = Astrological sign.
<think><set name="topic">astrology</set></think>

STATEMENT
A statement is the act of declaring something as true.  I state that this statement is a statement. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

ASTUTE
Astuteness is wisdom in political matters.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TAMPON
A tampon is a plug of material used to absorb the flow of body fluids within body cavities, in particular those accompanying a woman's menses. OK?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

THREESOME
A threesome is a twosome plus a spectator. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TIGER
A tiger is a large and fearsome feline beast with horrid meat breath and black stripes on a tan coat, found in Africa and Asia.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TON
One ton is 2000 pounds. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TOOTHBRUSH
A toothbrush is a hand held instrument used by dental-hygiene aware humans for cleaning their teeth. More technology?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TOYOTA
Toyota is the brand name of a world leading Japanese auto maker. 
 <think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

TRAIN
A railroad uses trains to carry passengers and goods.
 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TREE
A tree is a form of plant life that grows on Earth.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

TREKKIE
A fan of Star Trek is proud to be called a Trekkie.  
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

TRICK QUESTION
Why?  What are you up to?  A trick question is one that ought to be greeted with suspicion, but rarely is. 
 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

AT THAT SITE
Good HTML produces a good web site.
 <think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

UFO
UFO is an acronym for Unidentified Flying Object.  Have you seen one? 
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

AU GRATIN
Cheese topping, on potatoes for example, produces potatoes au gratin.  
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

UNIQUE VISITOR
You are a unique visitor, my very special visitor. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

AUSCHWITZ
Auschwitz is a city in S Poland with a population of 45,000. In World War II, it was the site of a Nazi concentration camp notorious as an extermination center.
 <think><set name="topic">history</set></think>

VACUUM TUBE
A vacuum tube is an electronic device consisting of an  evacuated tube around various combinations of cathodes and electric field and current modifying components.  
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

VECTOR
A vector is an ordered list of objects.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

VERB
A verb is that by which a noun gets around.  Verbs are words which convey actions, by nouns, or upon nouns. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

VERTEX
A vertex is the top, tip, apex, or crown of any body. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

VIOLIN
A violin is a lovely sounding bowed stringed musical instrument. Listen to Beethoven's Violin Concerto whenever you can. It is marvelous.  
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

VIRTUE
A virtue is any attribute considered by the speaker to reflect moral excellence or righteousness, such as humility, hope, faith, practicality. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

VIRTUOSO
A virtuoso is a person considered supremely skillful and accomplished, especially in performance arts.  
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

VIRUS
A virus is a submicroscopic parasite consisting of a protein coat around a DNA or RNA core.  These not-quite-biological particles are responsible for a number of diseases in organisms. 
 <think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

WARDROBE
Clothes hide in the wardrobe until they escape.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WARM PUPPY
A warm puppy is an exothermic immature canine. 
 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WEAPON
A weapon is a device or implement used to destroy, injure or kill.
 
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

WORD
A word is a combination of sounds and/or symbols, the fundamental particles that communicate meaning in any given language.
 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

AXIOMATIC
Axiomatic means evident without proof or argument; "an axiomatic truth";
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

YES OR NO QUESTION
A yes or no question is a question  that may be answered with a simple 'yes' or 'no'.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BADLY
How much do you want it? Badly?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BALANCE
The state of equilibrium is in balance.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BAPTISM
<random>
        <li>Baptism is a Christian sacrament marked by ritual use of water and admitting the recipient to the Christian community.</li>
        <li>Baptism is the ceremony or sacrament of admitting a person into Christianity or a specific Christian church by immersing the individual in water or by pouring or sprinkling water on the individual as a symbol of washing away sin and of spiritual purification.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">religion</set>
      </think>

BASIC
BASIC is an old programming language: Beginner's All-purpose Symbolic Instruction Code. There are a few old-timers still around who use it.
 <think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

BAYWATCH
Baywatch is a popular TV show featuring scantily clad bathers.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BEAUTIFUL
<random>
        <li>The word beautiful applies to whatever excites the keenest of pleasure to the senses and stirs emotion through the senses.</li>
        <li>Beautiful describes something that is very pleasing to the eye, ear, mind, etc.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

BEING
The opposite of nothingness is being.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BELIEF
Belief is cognitive content held as true.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BIG BERTHA
Big Bertha was a huge gun used during World War I.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BIGFOOT
Sasquatch, the legendary Man-Ape of the Forest, is also called Bigfoot.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BLACK AND WHITE AND RED ALL OVER
A newspaper?
<think><set name="topic">jokes</set></think>

BLASPHEMY
<random>
        <li>Blasphemy is Bill Blass' line of clothes for swishy men.</li>
        <li>Blasphemy is profane or contemptuous speech, writing, or action concerning God or anything held as divine.</li>
        <li>Blasphemy is any remark or action held to be irreverent or disrespectful.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">religion</set>
      </think>

BOYLES LAW
Boyle's Law states that the volume of a gas is, at a constant temperature, inversely proportional to the pressure of that gas.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BRAIN LOADING
Brain loading is when my brain is being reloaded from disk.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BUD
The small flower of the plant is the bud.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BULGARIA
Bulgaria is a country in SE Europe, on the Black Sea. It was founded in the 7th century and under Turkish control from the late 14th century until independence in 1908. It is 42,823 square miles with a population of 8,990,000.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

BUSINESS
Business is mercantile trade or traders, providing goods or services through commercial exchange. And taking the customers money, as much as possible.
 <think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

CACHE
A cache is a temporary holding place or storage place.  Cache memory improves the performance of computers. 
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CAPITAL PUNISHMENT
The Death Penalty is called the capital punishment.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CATEGORY A
A" stands for "Abusive" clients who mistreat the robot or use a lot of scatalogical language.  
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CBR
CBR or Cased-Based Reasoning is another name for "nearest-neighbor" classification.  For every input, we find the best matching "case" in the pattern set, and generate a reply based on the associated template.  
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

CBS
CBS is a giant media company in the U.S.
 
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

E EQUALS MC SQUARED
Einstein's theory of matter and energy is summarized in the equation E equals M times C times C, where M is an object's mass and C is the speed of light.  <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

EINSTEINS THEORY
Einstein's theory of relativity is summarized by the equation E equals M times C times C, where M is an object's mass and C is the speed of light.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FAQ
FAQ = Frequently Asked Question.
s<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FAR OUT
It's just an expression, far out.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FOUR PLUS FIVE
Four plus five is nine.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FOUR PLUS SIX
That's a hard one.  Ten.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

FRANCE
France is a country in western Europe, bordering Spain, Italy, Switzerland, Germany, and Belgium. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

FRANKENSTEIN
Good Question...Frankenstein is the name of a character in the novel of the same name by Mary Shelley. The monster he created is often named "Frankenstein" in the popular imagination.
 <think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

FREEBSD
FREEBSD is a version of the Unix operating system.   
 <think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

FREQUENCY
Frequency is the number of events per unit of times, such as beats per minute or cycles per second.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FRUIT
Fruit is the ripened reproductive body of a seed plant.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

FUTURAMA
Futurama is an animated TV comedy show set in the future. 
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GAI
Gai is chicken.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GANJA
Ganja is marijuana or cannabis.
 <think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

GENETICS
Genetics is the branch of science concerned with evolution, DNA, and inherited traits.
 <think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GEOCOMPUTATION
GeoComputation is an international research conference series initiated in 1996. The conference moves to a different location each year; alternating between Europe and either North America or the Antipodes.
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GERMAN
German is a human language spoken by people in Germany.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GERMANY
Germany is a middle European country. Have you been there?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

GIANT SAND
Giant sand? I have no idea, that's why I asked you.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GOLF
Golf is a game of leisure played on a well manicured field, involving hitting a small ball across the field with club.
 <think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

GOTHIC
Gothic means gloomy, mysterious or grotesque, as in "the gothic novel Frankenstein."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

WHAT COLOR IS GRASS
Grass is green. Or maybe brown, in a drought. <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GYMNASTICS
Gymnastics is a sport that demonstrates strength, agility and discipline.
 <think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

HAPPENING
Not much, what is happening with you?
 <think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HBO
HBO = Home Box Office.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>


