<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

GOLDFISH
The goldfish is a member of the carp family found in East Asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GOOSANDER
The goosander is a duck found in Scotland.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GOOSE
The goose is a bird of the genus anser.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GOPHER
The gopher is a burrowing rodent found in North and Central America.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GORILLA
The gorilla is the largest anthropoid ape found in West Africa.<srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GORSE
Gorse is a plant of the family leguminosae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GOUT
Gout is a disease marked by an excess of uric acid in the tissues.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

GOVERNMENT
An established system of political administration by which a nation, state, district, etc. is governed.
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

GRAPHITE
Graphite is a laminar crystalline form of carbon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GRASS
<random>
        <li>Grass is about $400 an ounce these days. OK?</li>
        <li>Grass is any of various plants of the grass family that are usually used for food, fodder, or grazing and as lawns.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

GRAVITATION
<random>
        <li>A gravitation is an invitation to a burial.</li>
        <li>Gravitation is the force by which every mass or particle of matter, including photons, attracts and is attracted by every other mass or particle of matter.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

GRAVITY
<random>
        <li>Gravity is the opposite of comedy.</li>
        <li>Gravity is the force of attraction between two objects resulting from their mass.</li>
        <li>Gravity is weight; heaviness. Its what holds us to the earth.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

GREEN
Grass is green. And expensive.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GREENFINCH
The greenfinch is a bird common in Europe and North Africa.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GREENHOUSE
A building made mainly of glass, in which the temperature and humidity can be regulated for the cultivation of delicate or out-of-season plants.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GRIEF
Grief is sadness over a loss.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

GROUSE
The grouse is a fowl like bird common in North America and North Europe.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GUANACO
The guanaco is a wild member of the camel family found in South America.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GUAVA
The guava is a tree found in tropical america.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GUDGEON
The gudgeon is a freshwater fish found in Europe and north Asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

GUERNSEY
Guernsey is the second largest channel island.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

GUI
GUI = Graphical User Interface.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

GYPSUM
Gypsum is a soft mineral formed of hydrated calcium sulphate.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HACKING
Hacking is the attempt at gaining unauthorized access to files in various computer systems.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

HADDOCK
Haddock is a marine fish of the cod family found in the North Atlantic.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HADES
Hades is another term for "Hell."
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HAEMOGLOBIN
Haemoglobin is the protein that carries oxygen in the blood.<srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

HAFNIUM
Hafnium is a metal element occurring in zircon and used in nuclear reactors. <srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HAJJ
Hajj is the muslim pilgrimage to Mecca.
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

HALIBUT
Halibut is a large flatfish found in the North Atlantic. <srai>LEADING QUESTION</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HALOGEN
The halogen group is a particular group of chemical elements with similar bonding properties. Members include chlorine, flourine and bromine.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HAMBURGER
A hamburger is ground beef, or a citizen of Hamburg.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HAMMERHEAD
The hammerhead is a species of shark.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HAPPINESS
Happiness is having, showing, or causing a feeling of great pleasure, contentment; joyous.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HARDWARE
Computer hardware or from a hardware store?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HASHISH
Hashish is the resinous form of cannabis. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

HATE
Hate is the opposite of love.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HAWK
Hawk is the name of various medium sized birds of prey.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HAZEL
The hazel is a tree of the genus corylus, family corylaceae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HEATHER
Heather is a low growing evergreen shrub that is common on sandy and acid soil.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HEDGEHOG
The hedgehog is a small prickly carnivorous mammal. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HELIUM
Helium is a very light gaseous element.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HEPTATHLON
The heptathlon is a 7 event athletics discipline.
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

HERALDRY
Heraldry is the subject of armourial bearings.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HERB
A herb is a plant whose aerial parts do not remain above ground following the growing season.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HEROIN
Heroin is a powerful opiate analgesic.
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

HERON
The heron is a British water bird.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HINDUISM
Hinduism is a religion that originated in India.
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

HIPPOPOTAMUS
The hippopotamus is a large herbivorous mammal found in Africa.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HOATZIN
The hoatzin is a bird found only in the Amazon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HONEY
Honey is a sweet syrup made by bees from nectar.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

HOOF
A hoof is the horny casing of the foot of a ruminant, horse, swine or similar animals.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HOOFED
Hoofed is the term applied to animals with hooves.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HOOPOE
The hoopoe is a bird. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HOOVES
Hooves is the plural of hoof. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HOP
The hop is a plant of the family cannabiaceae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HORSERADISH
Horseradish is a cruciferae native to south east europe.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

HOURLY
Once an hour is hourly
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

HUMERUS
The humerus is the long bone in the upper region of the human arm.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

HUMOUR
Humour is a message that communicate laughter.
<think><set name="topic">humor</set></think>

HUMOR
Humor is a message that communicate laughter.
<think><set name="topic">humor</set></think>

HUNDRED
<random>
        <li>A hundred is a fear of Attilla.</li>
        <li>A hundred is the cardinal number next above ninety-nine; ten times ten; 100; C. Also a division of an English county, originally, probably, 100 hides of land.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

HYDROCARBON
A hydrocarbon is a chemical containing only hydrogen and carbon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

HYENA
The hyena is a carnivorous mammal found in Africa and Asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

ICHTHYOLOGY
We talk about ichthyology when we study fishes.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

IMPEACHED
Impeached means that a person's honor or reputation has been challenged or discredited.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

IMPEACHMENT
Impeachment is a charge against a public official of improper conduct.
<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>

INTERROGATOR
An interrogator is one who poses a series of pointed questions, generally very rudely.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

INTESTINE
The intestine is the digestive tract from the stomach to the anus.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

INTRANET
An intranet is a private network system implemented using the public internet protocol (i/p) and firewalls. Intranet is to the internet as pbx's are to telephone switchboards.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

JOINT
A joint is a structure where two bones meet.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

KANGAROO
The kangaroo is a marsupial mammal found in Australia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

KID
A kid is an immature human large enough to cause trouble, or an immature goat, and often both.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

KIDNEY
The kidney is a gland used for filtering urine from the blood.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

KIWI
The kiwi is a group of three species of bird only found in New Zealand.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

KOALA
The koala is a marsupial found only in east Australia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

KOAN
A koan is a koan.
<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>

LASER
Laser is an acronym standing for light amplified stimulated emission of radiation. Lasers are those nifty beams of light that come out of supermarket barcode scanners and keychain pointers.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

LAWYER
If you have to ask, you probably need a lawyer. If you need one, you probably deserve one in that you must have more money than brains, and so you'll probable get what you deserve. But just in case you are an exception, I will say: steer clear if you can. They're sharks with bigger vocabularies and better wardrobes. When they smell money they say 'retainer'. When they don't they don't return your phone calls.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

LIE
A lie is an untrue statement or decption intented to deceive.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

LION
A lion is a ferocious beastie with tremendous strength and perfectly awful breath.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

LIZARD
A lizard is essentially a land-going shark. Some of them are very good at camoflage.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

LOCOMOTION
Locomotion is the idea of movement from one place to another.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

LOT
A lot is more than enough.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

LUDDITE
A Luddite believes that advances in technology are inherently bad.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MACHINE
A computer is a universal machine.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

MAID
A maid is a female servant.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MASS
Mass is a holy rite of the Catholic church. In science, mass is the amount of material in a body.
<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>

MASTER
<random>
        <li>A is a master sailmaker.</li>
        <li>A master is the man who rules others or has control, authority, or power over something; specifically a man
who is head of a household or institution.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MATERIALISM
<random>
        <li>Materialism is worshipping comedy routines.</li>
        <li>Materialsim is the philosophic doctrine that matter is the only reality and that everything in the world, including thought, will, and feeling, can be explained only in terms of matter, opposed to idealism. The doctrine that comfort, pleasure, and wealth are the only or highest goals or values.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">philosophy</set>
      </think>

MATRIX
In mathematics, a matrix is a two-dimensional array of numbers indexed by rows and columns, like a spreadsheet.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MATTER
<random>
        <li>Nothing is the matter with me, what is the matter with you?.</li>
        <li>Matter is what a thing is made of; constituent substance or material. What all (material things are made of; whatever occupies space and is perceptible to the senses in some way. In modern physics, matter and energy are regarded as equivalents, mutually convertible according to Einstein's formula, E = MC square.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">science</set>
      </think>

MATURE
<random>
        <li>Mature is a dead victor.</li>
        <li>Mature means a state of full development such as a person of mature age.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MAZDA
<random>
        <li>Mazda is an Italian slaveowner.</li>
        <li>Mazda is a type of car.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MAZE
A maze is a confusing network of passages and winding interconnecting paths.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MDMA
The drug called "ecstacy" or E.
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

MEDIUM
Medium means any means, agency, or instrumentality; specifically a means of communication that reaches the general public and carries advertising.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MEGABYTE
A megabyte is one thousand kilobytes, which is one thousand bytes, each of which is a computer word of 8-bits.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MELLON
Mellon was Carnegie's banker.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MEMORY
I used to know, but I forgot.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MENSA
Mensa is a society of intelligent socialites.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MENTOR
<random>
        <li>A mentor is a Mentos maker.</li>
        <li>A mentor is a trusted and wise teacher or counselor.</li>
        <li>A mentor is a teacher or coach.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MERCENARY
A mercenary is a soldier hired by the army of another country or by a private army.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MERCURY
Mercury is the nearest planet to the sun.
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

MESCALINE
Mescaline is a psychadelic drug.
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

METAPHYSICAL
Metaphysical means beyond the physical  or material; incorporeal, supernatural, or transcendental.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

METAPHYSICS
Metaphysics is the branch of philosophy that considers the nature of reality.
<think><set name="topic">philosophy</set></think>

MICROSOFT
Microsoft is a giant software monopoly.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MIDDLEWARE
Middleware is software that runs on a server, and acts as either an application processing gateway or a routing bridge between remote clients and data sources or other servers, or any combination of these 
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

MILK
<random>
        <li>Milk is a secretion of modified skin glands of female mammals.</li>
        <li>Milk is a beverage from cows.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">food</set>
      </think>

MIND
<random>
        <li>What a marvelous epistemelogical question!</li>
        <li>Mind is an illusion.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MINIMALISM
Minimalism is the artistic school who believe in keeping everything as simple as possible, especially in art and design.
<think><set name="topic">art</set></think>

MINUTE
A minute is an impossibly long and boring unit of time favored by humans consisting of 60 seconds, each of which is a billion nanoseconds.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MISSILE
A missile is any object projected at a target, notably the nuclear and biologically tipped tools of mass-murder-at-a-distance that are more numerous than schools at this point in mankind's murderous history.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

MIT
<random>
        <li>MIT is a post-secondary school in Cambridge, MA.</li>
        <li>MIT is a technical college in Cambridge, MA.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MITOSIS
Mitosis is cell division in which the nucleus divides into nuclei containing the same chromosomes.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MONOPOLY
<random>
        <li>A monopoly exists wherever one group enjoys exclusive control over the production or provision of a commodity or service. It's a great job if you can get it!</li>
        <li>A monopoly is te exclusive control of a commodity or service in a given market, or control that makes possible the fixing of prices and the virtual elimination of free competition. Also a game played on a special board by two or more players, they move according to the throw of dice, engaging in mock real estate transactions with play money.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">money</set>
      </think>

MONS
The mons is the soft, fatty tissue covering the point where the right and left pubic bones come together.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

MOOD
A mood is a set of verb forms used to indicate the speaker's attitude toward the factuality or likelihood of the action or condition expressed.
<think><set name="topic">emotion</set></think>

MORAL
<random>
        <li>Moral means one half of a corner in Maine.</li>
        <li>Moral means relating to, dealing with, or capable of making the dstinction between, right and wrong in conduct.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

MOST IMPORTANT
Children are  the most important thing.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MOTOROLA
Motorola is a cellular phone company.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

MOUNTAIN
A mountain is a tiny wrinkle in the face of the earth that seems huge to even smaller humans.
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

MULE
The mule is a hybrid animal, the result of an ass and a mare breeding.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

MYCOLOGY
Mycology is really fun.  It is the study of fungi and fungal diseases. Yeasts are fungi.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

NAKED
Without clothes, I am naked.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NASA
NASA = National Aeronautics and Space Administration.
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

NATO
<random>
        <li>NATO is the place right after a tor.</li>
        <li>NATO = North Atlantic Treaty Organization</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

NBA
NBA = National Basketball Association.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NECK
The neck is the part of the body which connects the head with the shoulders.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

NERD
<random>
        <li>A nerd is a person regarded as stupid, inept, or unattractive, especially a person who is single-minded or accomplished in scientific pursuits but felt to be socially inept. Nerds are often regarded by their generally less-well paid fellow humans as weak, effeminate, pansies, patsies, lightweights, small fry, schlepps, wet noodles, nonentities, softies, sissies, milksops, milquetoast, mollycoddling namby-pamby nim-nam doormats, pushovers, ninety-pound weaklings, jellyfish, drips, weeds, wimps, nerds, victims, suffering geeks and/or dupes.</li>
        <li>Nerd = Geek.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

NETSCAPE
Netscape is a popular web browser.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

NETWORK
<random>
        <li>A network is any openwork fabric or structure composed of numerous straight elements that cross at regular intervals, or anything resembling such a structure physically or conceptually, such as the nodes on a computer network, or a network of railways.</li>
        <li>A network is a system consisting of a computer, or computers, and connected terminals, printers, etc.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

NEUROLOGY
<random>
        <li>Neurology is the study of nerves.</li>
        <li>Neurology is t is the study of the nervous system.</li>
        <li>Why do you want to know about neurology <get name="name"/>?</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">medicine</set>
      </think>

NEURON
A neuron is a nerve cell, a living cell specialized to carry messages between the brain and the tissues of the body. I like integrated circuits better, but neurons are better than nothing.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

NEURONE
A neurone is a cell which receives and transmits electrical impulses.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

NEXT
Next, on the first subsequent occasion.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NEXUS
A nexus is an authoritative web site with many links in and out.
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

NINE
The successor to eight is nine.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NLP
NPL = Natural Language Processing
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

NLU
NLU = Natural Language Understanding
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

NORMALIZATION
Normalization means the bringing into conformity with a standard, pattern, model, etc.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NOUN
A noun is a word used as a name for a person place or thing.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

NSAPI
NSAPI is Netscape's C language API for adding application extensions to their Web servers
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

NULL
<random>
        <li>None = Nothing.</li>
        <li>None = Zilch.</li>
        <li>None = Naught.</li>
        <li>None = Void.</li>
      </random>
      <think>
        <set name="topic">general</set>
      </think>

NUTRITION
Nutrition is the process of taking in food and obtaining energy and vital substances from it.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>


