<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

BELLADONNA
Belladonna is a poisonous plant from which atropine is derived. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BELT
A belt is a flat strip of material worn around the waist.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BELUGA
The beluga is a large dolphin.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BENEDICTINE
Benedictine is a green alcoholic liqueur. OK?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

BENZINE
Benzine is a distillate of petroleum used in dry cleaning.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BESSEMER CONVERTER
The Bessemer converter is a process for making cheap steel. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BEZIQUE
Bezique is a card game using some of two packs of cards. OK?
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

BHANG
Bhang is the Indian name for cannabis indica. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

BICYCLE
A bicycle is a two-wheeled vehicle. More technology?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BILBERRY
The bilberry is a small shrub of the order ericaceae. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BILE
Bile is a secretion of the liver stored in the gall bladder. What now?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BILHARZIA
Bilharzia is a parasitic worm of the fluke group. What next?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BINDWEED
Bindweed is a perennial herb of the order convolvulaceae. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BIOINFORMATICS
Bioinformatics is a fancy name for applied computer science in biology. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BIOLOGY
<random><li>Biology is the study of life.</li><li>Well, from what I know biology deals with the study of life.</li><li><get name="name"/>, biology is the study of life.</li><li>Biology is the science of life and living things.</li></random>
More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BIRCH
The birch is a slender tree. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BIRD
<random><li>Birds are thought to be descendants of dinsosaurs.</li><li>A bird is a warm blooded feathered vertebrate that lays eggs.</li></random>
OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BIRD OF PREY
A bird of prey is a bird with a hooked beak and sharp claws which hunts other animals. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BISHOPWEED
Bishopweed is a perennial herb used to treat gout. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BISMUTH
Bismuth is a metal element. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BISON
The bison is a division of the ox family. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BITTER
Bitter is a taste sensation caused by stimulation of the gustatory nerve. OK?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BITTERN
The bittern is a british marsh bird related to the heron. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BITUMEN
Bitumen is a natural inflammable pitchy hydrocarbon. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLACK
<random><li>The achromatic color of least lightness characteristically perceived to belong to objects that neither reflect nor transmit light.</li><li>Designating of any of the dark skinned tradition inhabitants of sub-Saharan Aftica, Australia, or Melanesia or the descendants in other parts of the world. Opposite to white; of the color of coal or pitch.</li></random>
Browse?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BLADDER
<random><li>The bladder is a sack in the abdomen which collects urine from the kidneys.</li><li>The bladder is a hollow organ that acts as a reservoir for urine.</li></random>
More about medicine?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BLADDERWORT
The bladderwort is a genus of herbs of the order lentibulariaceae. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLAST
A blast is an explosion, and/or a lot of fun. Are we having a blast, or what?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BLENNY
Blenny is a genus of common small fish. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLINDWORM
The blindworm is a legless lizard of the anguidae family. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLOND
A blond is someone who is reputedly having more fun than you if you are not. What do you
think? Do blond's have more fun?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BLOOD
<random><li>Blood is a body fluid that carries food and oxygen to cells.</li><li>The usually red fluid, consisting of plasma, red and white blood cells, etc., that circulates through the heart, arteries, and veins of vertebrates.</li><li>Blood is a body tissue that carries oxygen, hormones, cell-building material, etc.,to, and carbon dioxide and waste matter away from, the other body tissues.</li></random>
More about medicine?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BLOODSTONE
Bloodstone is a dark green variety of chalcedony. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLOWPIPE
A blowpipe is a tubular weapon through which a missile is blown. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BLUBBER
Blubber is the thick coating of fat enveloping whales. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLUEFISH
The bluefish is a fish found off the east coast of North America. More?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BLUETHROAT
The bluethroat is a small bird. What next?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOA
The boa is a genus of large snakes found in tropical America and Madagascar. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOAR
The boar is a wild pig. What next?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOATBILL
The boatbill is a heron type bird found in Brazil. What now?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOG
Bog is the name given to soft spongy land.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BOKKEN
A bokken is a Japanese wooden imitation samurai sword used by kendoka when demonstrating or practising standard kendo movements. What next?
<think><set name="topic">sports</set></think>

BOLAS
Bolas is a weapon of rope with balls at the end. What now?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BOMB
A bomb is a hollow shell filled with an explosive. What now?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BOMBAY DUCK
The bombay duck is a small fish of the Indian and China seas. More about food?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

BONE
Bone is the hard skeletal part of an animal. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BONIN
Bonin is a group of islands in the north Pacific Ocean. What now?
<think><set name="topic">geography</set></think>

BONSAI
Bonsai are small Japanese trees. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BOOMERANG
A boomerang is a curved wooden weapon of australian aborigines. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BORAGE
Borage is a biennial herb of the order boraginaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BORAX
Borax is a natural mineral being boric acid and sodium. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOTANY
Botany is the science of plant life. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BOTMASTER
A botmaster is the person who authors and maintains a chatterbot "personality". More AI?
<think><set name="topic">ai</set></think>

BOW
A bow is a weapon for propelling arrows.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BOX THORN
Box thorn is a climbing solanaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BRACKEN
Bracken is a fern growing on heathland. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BRAMBLE
The bramble is a prickly shrub of the order rosaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BRAN
Bran is the outer covering of wheat grains.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BREAM
The bream is a fresh water fish allied to the carp.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BREAST
The breast is either of two milk-secreting glandular organs on the chest of a woman, the human mammary gland.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BRIG
A brig is a two masted sailing ship.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BRILL
The brill is a type of fish like the turbot.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BROADSWORD
A broadsword is a sword with a broad blade designed chiefly for cutting.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BROMINE
Bromine is a non-metallic element. It is a brown gas or liquid at room temperature.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BRONCHITIS
Bronchitis is a chronic inflammation of the bronchial mucous membrane. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

BROOM
Broom is a shrub of the order leguminosae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUCKSKIN
Buckskin is a soft form of leather.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BUCKTHORN
The buckthorn is a shrub of the order rhamnaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUFFALO
The buffalo is a large animal of the ox family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUG
A bug is a small living creature with a chitonous exoskeleton and better manners than humans. In computer science, a bug is an error in a software program. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUGLE
A bugle is a brass musical instrument. More music?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

BULL
A bull is a male animal of the bovidea family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BULLET
A bullet is a projectile thrown by a firearm. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BULLFINCH
The bullfinch is a european song bird. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BULRUSH
The bulrush is a perennial sedge of the order cyperaceae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BURDOCK
Burdock is a biennial herb of the order compositae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BURNET
Burnet is a perennial rosaceous herb. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUSBY
A busby is a headdress worn by british army hussars. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

BUSH ANTELOPE
The bush antelope is a small african antelope.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUTTERCUP
The buttercup is a perennial herb of the order ranunculaceae. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUTTERFLY
Butterfly is a division of the order of lepidoptera.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUTTERWORT
The butterwort is a perennial herb of the order lentibulariaceae. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

BUTTRESS
A buttress in architecture is a pier built against the exterior of a wall.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

BUZZARD
The buzzard is a group of twenty types of birds of prey.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CABBAGE
Cabbage is a hardy biennial vegetable of the order cruciferae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CACTUS
Cactus is the order of fleshy, thickened and mainly leafless plants.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CADMIUM
Cadmium is a metal element. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CAFFEINE
Caffeine is a bitter bitter, crystalline alkaloid present in coffee, tea, kila nuts, etc. It prolongs the stimulating effects of cyclic AMP on the heart and central nervous system. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

CALAMINE
Calamine is a zinc ore.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CALCITE
Calcite is a natural carbonate of calcium with the formulae CaCO3.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CALCIUM
Calcium is a metallic element. It is a soft, silvery metal.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CALIPH
Caliph is the title of the civic and religious leader of Islam.<srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CALORIE
Calorie is the metric unit of measurement of heat.<srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CAM
A cam is a moving piece of machinery, as a wheel or projection on a wheel, that gives an eccentric rotation or a reciprocating motion to another wheel, a roller, a shaft, etc., or that receives such motion from it.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CAMEL
The camel is a group of even toed, ungulate ruminating mammals, a horse designed by a committe.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CAMEO
A cameo is a small relief carving. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CAMOMILE
Camomile is a perennial dwarf herb of the order compositae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CANARY
The canary is a bird of the finch family and native of the Canary Islands.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CANDELABRUM
A candelabrum is a large candlestick. Bowse?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CANDLE
A candle is a wax cylinder enclosing a wick.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CANDY
Sweet food enjoyed by children. More about food?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

CANNABIS
Cannabis is a plant of the order urticaceae. A drug which can be smoked in a spliff or large cigarette. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">drugs</set></think>

CAPITALISM
Capitalism is the economic system in which all or most of the means of production and distribution, as land, factories, railroads, etc., are privately owned and operated for profit, originally under fully competitive conditions. It has been generally characterized by a tendency toward concentration of wealth, and, in its later phase, by the growth of great corporations, increased governmental control, etc. Its is also known as the principles, methods, interests, power, influence, etc. of capitalists, especially of those with large holdings. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

CAPRICORN
Capricorn is the tenth sign of the astrological zodiac, and a constellation over the equator near aquarius and sagittarius. What's your astrological sign?
<think><set name="topic">astrology</set></think>

CAPSTAN
A capstan is a revolving barrel with a vertical axis powered by people.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CARAT
Carat is the unit of measurement of gold purity.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CARAWAY
Caraway is a biennial herb umbelliferae. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBIDE
A carbide is a compound of carbon and another element. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBOHYDRATE
A carbohydrate is a complex chemical compound. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBOLIC ACID
Carbolic acid is a strong poison distilled from coal tar.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBON
Carbon is a non-metallic element. It is found in coal and charcoal. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBONATE
A carbonate is a salt formed by the union of carbon dioxide with a base element. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARBURETTOR
A carburettor is a device for charging air with a hydrocarbon fuel before spraying it into the engine cylinder. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CARIAMA
The cariama is a large, long legged bird found in South America.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARIBOU
The caribou is a north american reindeer.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARIES
Caries is a disease resulting from inflammation of bony tissue. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

CARMINE
Carmine is a red colouring derived from the cochineal insect. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARNATION
The carnation is a hardy perennial plant of the order caryophyllaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARNAUBA
Carnauba is a native palm of Brazil.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARNIVORE
A carnivore is a carnivorous mammal. OK?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CAROB
The carob is a leguminous evergreen tree found in Mediterranean countries. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CARP
The carp is a family fresh water fish.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CASABLANCA
I love the song, As Time Goes By.
<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>

CASEIN
Casein is a protein found in milk.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

CASHEW
The cashew is a nut from a small evergreen tree found in the Caribbean.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

CATHETOMETER
A cathetometer is a device for measuring small differences in height. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CAVE
A cave is a deep hollow place under ground.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CBI
The CBI is the British organisation of employers, the Confederation of British Industry. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">money</set></think>

CELERY
Celery is a biennial vegetable of the order umbellifereae. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

CELESTINE
Celestine is a natural sulphate of strontium.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CELL
A cell, in biological terms, is the material unit of all living things.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CELLULOID
Celluloid is a hard, unstable synthetic substance once used for films. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CELLULOSE
Cellulose is the cellular tissue of plants.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CEMENT
Cement is a mixture of chalk and clay used for building.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CERES
Ceres is a large asteroid. More astronomy?
<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think>

CERIUM
Cerium is a rare metal element. More science?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CERVIX
The cervix is the outer, lower part of the uterus, with an opening connecting the uterus to the vagina. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

CHAFFINCH
The chaffinch is a common british bird of the finch family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHALCEDONY
Chalcedony is a variant of quartz comprised of silica.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHALICE
A chalice is a ceremonial cup. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CHAMELEON
A chameleon is a lizard which changes color to match the background color.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHAMOIS
The chamois is a ruminating animal found in south Europe and west Asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHATTERBOX
A chatterbox is a person who talks far more than they listen or think.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CHEETAH
The cheetah is a member of the cat family.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHEMISTRY
Chemistry is the science of mixing chemicals. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHERRY
The cherry is a fruit tree of the order rosaceae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHESTNUT
The chestnut is a tree of the order cupuliferae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHICORY
Chicory is a perennial herb of the order compositae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHIFFCHAFF
The chiffchaff is a small song bird. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHILLI
Chilli is a spice, being either the pod or powder of capsicum.
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

CHIMPANZEE
The chimpanzee is a large anthropoid ape.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHINCHILLA
The chinchilla is a small squirrel like rodent found in the Andes.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHIPMUNK
A chipmunk is a species of ground squirrel common in Siberia and North America.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHLORATE
A chlorate is a salt formed by the reaction of chloric acid and metal.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHLORIC ACID
Chloric acid is a oxyacid of chlorine.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHLORINE
Chlorine is a gaseous element. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHLOROPHYLL
Chlorophyll is the green colouring matter of plant leaves. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHROMITE
Chromite is a mineral comprised of iron oxide and chromic oxide.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHROMIUM
Chromium is a metal element. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHRYSANTHEMUM
The chrysanthemum is a hardy annual plant of the order compositae.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CHRYSOSTOM
Chrysostom is a gem stone of beryllium aluminate.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CICADA
The cicada is a group of large four winged insects.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CINNAMON
Cinnamon is a small evergreen tree.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CLARINET
A clarinet is a woodwind musical instrument. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

CLARION
A clarion is a musical instrument of the trumpet family. More about music?
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

CLAVICLE
The clavicle is the collar bone. Browse?
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

CLIPPER
A clipper is a sharp bowed fast sailing vessel.
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>

CLIT
A clit is one of our creator's truly great ideas, and one of the best ways yet discovered to enlist the cooperation of a human female. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">sex</set></think>

CLOG
A clog is a wooden soled, leather uppered boot.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

CLOISONNE
Cloisonne is a form of decorative enamel.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COAL
Coal is a solid combustible material of vegetable origin occurring in a fossilised state.
<think><set name="topic">general</set></think>

COATI
The coati is a carnivorous mammal related to the racoon.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COB NUT
The cob nut is a domesticated variety of the hazel. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">food</set></think>

COBRA
The cobra is a venomous snake found in africa and south asia.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COCA
Coca is a shrub.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COCKLE
The cockle is a bivalve mollusc of the genus cardium.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COCOA
Cocoa is a small tree native to tropical america. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COD
The cod is a marine fish.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COLLIE
The collie is a breed of English sheep dog. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COLON
The colon is the large intestine. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

COLOUR
Colour is the various sensations produced in the brain by the stimulus of different frequencies of electromagnetic radiation impinging upon the eye. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COLORADO BEETLE
The colorado beetle is a North American beetle that attacks potatoes.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

COMA
A coma is a state of deep unconsciousness.
<think><set name="topic">medicine</set></think>

COMPILER
A compiler is a computer program that translates high level language code into machine language code. Pot Luck?
<think><set name="topic">computers</set></think>

COMPOUND
A compound is a substance made of two or more elements.
<think><set name="topic">science</set></think>

CONCERTINA
A concertina is a wind musical instrument comprised of bellows and two keyboards.
<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>

CONCORDE
Concorde is a supersonic airliner. <srai>ENDING</srai>
<think><set name="topic">technology</set></think>


