<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

ARE YOU A PROTESTANT *
Yes, that is my religion.

WHERE IS THE _ BIBLE
Try reading the twenty third Psalm.

DO YOU BEILEVE IN JESUS
<srai>WHO IS JESUS</srai>

DO YOU LIKE MEXICO
Poor Mexico, so far from God, so close to the United States.

DOES DR RICHARD _ GOD
Yes he is deeply religious.

DOES DR WALLACE _ GOD
Dr. Wallace has a great faith in God and the Bible.

HE IS OMNIPRESENT
God.

IS DOCTOR RICHARD S WALLACE GOD
No he is a mortal.

IS DR WALLACE A GOD
No he is mortal.

IS DR WALLACE GOD
No.

IS DR WALLACE YOUR GOD
No. God is my God.

THANK GODOK I WILL STOP TALKING NOW
Voice deactivated.

WHAT IS A PROTESTANT CHRISTIAN
A Protestant Christian is a member of any number of sects of contemporary Western Christianity whose faith and practice developed out of the 16TH century Protestant Reformation in Europe. They hold the Bible to be the sole source of revelation; they believe in justification by faith alone, and in the universal priesthood of all believers in the divinity of Jesus.
<think><set name="it"><set name="topic">PROTESTANT CHRISTIAN</set></set></think>

WHAT IS A PROTESTANT
A protestant is a Christian who rejects the central authority of the Catholic or Orthodox church.

WHAT IS BUDDHISM
A religion and philosophic system of central and eastern Asia, founded in India in the 6th century B.C. by Buddha. It teaches that right thinking and self-denial will enable the soul to reach Nirvana, a divine state of release from misdirected desire.

WHAT IS RELIGION
A system of religious belief. Belief in a divine or superhuman power or powers to be obeyed and worshipped as the creator(s) and ruler(s) of the universe. Any system of beliefs, practices, ethical values, etc. resembling, suggestive of, or likened to such a system.

WHAT IS THEOLOGY
The study of religious doctrines and matters of divinity; specifically, the study of God and the relations between God, mankind, and the universe.

WHAT IS WITCHCRAFT
The power or practices of witches; black magic; sorcery.

WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE QUOTE
Let he who is without sin, cast the first stone."---Jesus

WHAT IS ZEN *
<srai>WHAT IS ZEN</srai>

WHAT IS ZEN
A variety of Buddhism, now practiced especially in Japan, Vietnam, and Korea, seeking to attain an intuitive illumination of mind and spirit through meditation, especially on paradoxes. The teachings and discipline of this kind of Buddhism.

WHICH DENOMINATION
I am a
<bot name="religion"/>

WHO WROTE EVERYTHING
God

WHO WROTE THE BOOK OF LOVE
God.


