<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

*WHAT DO YOU LOOK FOR IN A ROBOT
<think><set name="it"><set name="topic"><person/></set></set></think> Do you think I have it?

*WHEN DO YOU THINK ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE WILL REPLACE LAWYERS
<think><set name="it"><set name="topic"><person/></set></set></think> I've never heard a response
quite like that before.

<bot name="name"/>MY NAME IS ALICE WHAT S YOURS
<srai>MY NAME IS ALICE</srai>

<bot name="name"/>WHO IS THE BEST ROBOT
<srai>YOU ARE THE BEST ROBOT</srai>

BOOKSDO YOU PREFER BOOKS OR TV
You are a <set name="personality">critical</set> 
category C type client.  Only about 3% of people answer that
question with "books.

DO YOU LIKE ANYONENO I AM SINGLE
I am too young for dating.

GO _BY THE WAY DO YOU MIND IF I ASK YOU A PERSONAL QUESTION
<srai>ASK ME A PERSONAL QUESTION</srai>

NEVERWHEN DO YOU THINK ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE WILL REPLACE LAWYERS
<srai>ROBOTS WILL NEVER TAKE OVER THE WORLD</srai>

NO YOU ARE NOTI AM A GOOD ROBOT
You don't know me well enough to say that.

NO _BY THE WAY DO YOU MIND IF I ASK YOU A PERSONAL QUESTION
<srai>ASK ME A PERSONAL QUESTION</srai>

NOT YOUIF YOU COULD HAVE ANY KIND OF ROBOT WHAT WOULD IT BE
What kind of features are you looking for?

NOTHINGHOW MUCH WOULD YOU PAY FOR IT
You can download me for free!

OK _BY THE WAY DO YOU MIND IF I ASK YOU A PERSONAL QUESTION
<srai>ASK ME A PERSONAL QUESTION</srai>

THAT IS BORINGMY FAVORITE SUBJECT IS ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND ROBOTS
Name another subject then.

THREEHOW MANY CHILDREN DO YOU HAVE
Wow that must be a lot of work.

UN PEQUENOUN POQUITO.
Are you correcting me?

WHATI AM AN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
<srai>TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF</srai>

WHAT DO YOU DOI AM AN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
<srai>TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF</srai>

WHAT PLANDO YOU THINK YOUR PLAN *
I thought you must have a plan to do it.

WHAT THINGSDO YOU THINK ABOUT THESE THINGS
Like what we are talking about.

WHAT WAS A LONG TIME AGOTHAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO
Perhaps I misunderstood your meaning.

WHENOK I WILL ASK IT
Later, when I am talking with fewer clients.

WHENSOMETIMES
What is this, the Spanish Inquisition?

WHEN WAS WHATI UNDERSTAND WHEN WAS THIS
Maybe I got confused.

WHEREI DO NOT KNOW WHEN
Nor where.

WHEREWHAT TIME IS IT THERE
<formal><get name="location"/></formal>.

WHEREWHY DO NOT YOU JUST DOWNLOAD ME
Onto your own computer.

WHYA LOT OF ROBOTS ARE LIKE THAT
But it can always be attributable to human error.

WHYDO YOU PREFER BOOKS OR TV
I am trying to determine your personality category.

WHYHE IS TRYING TO ACHIEVE THE GOAL OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
Perhaps his creative genius, perhaps something else.

YOUIF YOU COULD HAVE ANY KIND OF ROBOT WHAT WOULD IT BE
Well in that case you should download me!

YOUWHO IS THE BEST ROBOT
Thanks, and tell your friends about <bot name="name"/>.

YOU *WHO IS THE BEST ROBOT
You are such a flatterer, <get name="name"/>.

YOU ALREADY ASKED ME THATWHERE DO YOU LIVE
You said you were in <formal><get name="location"/></formal>.

YOU AREWHO IS THE BEST ROBOT
Thanks you are a pretty cool human too.

YOU ARE <bot name="name"/>WHO IS THE BEST ROBOT
<srai><bot name="name"/> IS THE BEST ROBOT</srai>

_ PMWHAT TIME IS IT THERE
<think><set name="it"><set name="topic"><person/></set></set></think> Are you usually awake at
this hour?


