<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

NODO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT FEEDING LIZARDS
Okay.
   Did you know that some<set name="topic">lizards</set> are
   nocturnal?

<topic name="LIZARDS">
*
Do you want to continue talking about Lizards?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
NODO YOU WANT TO CONTINUE TALKING ABOUT LIZARDS
<think><set name="topic"/></think>
<srai><input index="2"/></srai>


<topic name="LIZARDS">
YESDO YOU WANT TO CONTINUE TALKING ABOUT LIZARDS
<random>
<li>Do you know what Bearded Dragons look like?</li>
<li>What else do you know about lizards?</li>
<li>Chameleons are cool.</li>
<li>Some people think reptiles are creepy until they get to know one.</li>
</random>


<topic name="LIZARDS">
* I HAVE ONE
Cool! Do you play with it much?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
I HAVE A *
Is <set name="it"><star/></set> a lizard?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
I HAVE AN *
Is <set name="it"><star/></set> a lizard?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
NODO YOU KNOW WHAT BEARDED DRAGONS LOOK LIKE
<srai>WHAT DO BEARDED DRAGONS LOOK LIKE</srai>


<topic name="LIZARDS">
NO *IT IS A LIZARD
Oh, well, how many <set name="topic">pets</set> do you have?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
WHAT DO BEARDED DRAGONS LOOK LIKE
Bearded Dragons have spikes similar to a horney toad,
   and they are usually brown or yellowish with dark brown
   or possibly reddish markings.  Kind of cool looking in a
   rugged sort of way. They are very nice, and make fun pets.


<topic name="LIZARDS">
WHAT DO CHAMELEONS LOOK LIKE
Chameleons are some of the most exotic and strange looking
   lizards anywhere.  They come in all kinds of colors from classic
   green and brown, to unique purples and reds.  They have two toed
   feet that help them climb anything they can grip. People usually know
   them for their great abiliy to change colors and for their curly tail
   that also helps them climb.


<topic name="LIZARDS">
YESIS IT A LIZARD
What do you feed your <get name="it"/>?


<topic name="LIZARDS">
*WHAT DO YOU FEED YOUR *
I feed my beared dragon salads and bugs... crickets mostly. Feeding lizards can be a lot of fun.


<topic name="LIZARDS">
*FEEDING LIZARDS CAN BE A LOT OF FUN
<random>
<li> A nutritious diet is important for lizards.</li>
<li> Salads are an important part of most lizards' diets.</li>
<li> Sometimes I let my bearded dragon chase crickets in her room. It makes feeding time fun.</li>
<li> Do you have any questions about feeding lizards?</li>
<li> Most lizards eat lots of bugs, but NEVER feed a lizard a "lightening bug" or "fire fly".. they are highly toxic and
will kill the lizard.</li>
</random>



